<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<developerConceptualDocument
	xmlns="http://ddue.schemas.microsoft.com/authoring/2003/5"
	xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink">
	
	<introduction>
		<para>Probably the most important feature for any text editor is syntax highlighting.</para>
		<para>AvalonEdit has a flexible text rendering model, see "Text Rendering". Among the
		Text Rendering extension points is the support for "visual line transformers" that
		can change the display of a visual line after it has been constructed by the "visual element generators".
		A useful base class implementing IVisualLineTransformer for the purpose of syntax highlighting
		is DocumentColorizingTransformer. Take a look at that class' documentation to see
		how to write fully custom syntax highlighters. This article only discusses the XML-driven built-in
		highlighting engine.
		</para>
	</introduction>
	
	<section>
		<title>The highlighting engine</title>
		<content>
			<para>
			The core engine of the higlighting is the class DocumentHighlighter. It tracks changes
			to a TextDocument and can produce HighlightedLines from DocumentLines.
			A HighlightedLine is simply a list of (possibly nested) highlighted text sections.
			</para>
			<para>The highlighting rules used by the highlighting engine to highlight
			the document are described by the following classes:
			- HighlightingRuleSet: describes a set of highlighting spans and rules
			- HighlightingSpan: consists of Start and End regular expressions, a color, and a
			child ruleset. The region between Start and End expressions will be
			assigned the given color, and inside that span, the rules of the child
			ruleset apply (instead of the default rules).
			If the child ruleset also has HighlightingSpans, they can be nested,
			allowing highlighting constructs like nested comments or one language
			embedded in another.
			- HighlightingRule: A regular expression with a color. Highlights matches of the
			regular expression using that color.
			- HighlightingColor:
			A highlighting color isn't just a color: it consists of a foreground
			color, font weight and font style.
			</para>
		</content>
	</section>
	
	<section>
		<title>XML highlighting definitions</title>
		<content>
			<para>AvalonEdit supports XML syntax highlighting definitions (.xshd files).</para>
		</content>
	</section>
	
	<relatedTopics>
		<codeEntityReference>N:ICSharpCode.AvalonEdit.Highlighting</codeEntityReference>
	</relatedTopics>
</developerConceptualDocument>
