<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<CodeDoc>
	<Class name="InertButton">
		<ClassDef>
			<summary>Image button with flat appearance, border visible only when activated by mouse.</summary>
		</ClassDef>
		<Constructor name="Overloads">
			<overloads>
				<summary>Initializes a new instance of the <see cref="WeifenLuo.WinFormsUI.InertButton" /> class.</summary>
			</overloads>
		</Constructor>
		<Constructor name="()">
			<summary>Initializes a new instance of the <see cref="WeifenLuo.WinFormsUI.InertButton" /> class, with default settings.</summary>
		</Constructor>
		<Constructor name="(Image)">
			<summary>Initializes a new instance of the <see cref="WeifenLuo.WinFormsUI.InertButton" /> class, with specified image for enabled button.</summary>
			<param name="imageEnabled">
			The <see cref="System.Drawing.Image" /> object to show when the button is enabled. The disabled image will be draw based on this image.
		</param>
		</Constructor>
		<Constructor name="(Image, Image)">
			<summary>Initializes a new instance of the <see cref="WeifenLuo.WinFormsUI.InertButton" /> class, with specified images for enabled and disabled button.</summary>
			<param name="imageEnabled">
			The <see cref="System.Drawing.Image" /> object to show when the button is enabled.
		</param>
			<param name="imageDisabled">
			The <see cref="System.Drawing.Image" /> object to show when the button is disabled.
		</param>
		</Constructor>
		<Property name="BorderColor">
			<summary>Gets or sets the border color for the control.</summary>
			<value>A <see cref="System.Drawing.Color" /> object that represents the border color of the control.</value>
		</Property>
		<Property name="BorderWidth">
			<summary>Gets or sets the border width for the control.</summary>
			<value>A integer that represents the border width for the control, in pixel. The default is <b>1</b>.</value>
		</Property>
		<Property name="ImageDisabled">
			<summary>Gets or sets the image to display for the control when disabled.</summary>
			<value>A <see cref="System.Drawing.Image" /> object to display for the control when disabled.</value>
		</Property>
		<Property name="ImageEnabled">
			<summary>Gets or sets the image to display for the control when enabled.</summary>
			<value>A <see cref="System.Drawing.Image" /> object to display for the control when enabled.</value>
		</Property>
		<Property name="ImageIndexDisabled">
			<summary>Gets or sets the index of the image to display for the control when disabled.</summary>
			<value>The zero-base index of the image in the <see cref="System.Windows.Forms.ImageList" /> to display for the control when disabled.</value>
		</Property>
		<Property name="ImageIndexEnabled">
			<summary>Gets or sets the index of the image to display for the control when enabled.</summary>
			<value>The zero-base index of the image in the <see cref="System.Windows.Forms.ImageList" /> to display for the control when enabled.</value>
		</Property>
		<Property name="ImageList">
			<summary>Gets or sets the <see cref="System.Windows.Forms.ImageList" /> that contains the images to display.</summary>
			<value>The <see cref="System.Windows.Forms.ImageList" /> that contains the images to display.</value>
		</Property>
		<Property name="IsPopup">
			<summary>Determines if the buttons is displayed as popup when activated.</summary>
			<value><b>True</b> if the button is displayed as popup when activated; otherwise <b>false</b>. The default value is <b>true</b>.</value>
		</Property>
		<Property name="Monochrome">
			<summary>Determines if the button is displayed as black and white.</summary>
			<value><b>True</b> if the button is displayed as as black and white; otherwise <b>false</b>. The default value is <b>false</b>.</value>
		</Property>
		<Property name="RepeatClick">
			<summary>Determines if the button will generate repeat click event when mouse is holding down.</summary>
			<value><b>True</b> if the button will generate repeat click event when mouse is holding down; otherwise <b>false</b>. The default value is <b>false</b>.</value>
			<remarks>The interval of generating repeat click is determined by <see cref="WeifenLuo.WinFormsUI.InertButton.RepeatClickDelay"/> and
			<see cref="WeifenLuo.WinFormsUI.InertButton.RepeatClickInterval" /> properties.</remarks>
		</Property>
		<Property name="RepeatClickDelay">
			<summary>Gets or sets the amount of time, in milliseconds, the <see cref="WeifenLuo.WinFormsUI.InertButton" />
			waits while it is pressed before it starts repeating. The value must be non-negative.</summary>
			<value>The default value is 500 milliseconds.</value>
		</Property>
		<Property name="RepeatClickInterval">
			<summary>Gets or sets the amount of time, in milliseconds, between repeats once repeating 
			starts. The value must be non-negative.</summary>
			<value>The default value is 100 milliseconds.</value>
		</Property>
		<Property name="TextAlign">
			<summary>Gets or sets the alignment of the text in the button.</summary>
			<value>One of the <see cref="System.Drawing.ContentAlignment" /> values. The default is <b>MiddleCenter</b>.</value>
		</Property>
		<Property name="ToolTipText">
			<summary>Gets or sets the ToolTip text for this button.</summary>
			<value>The ToolTip text for this button.</value>
		</Property>
	</Class>
</CodeDoc>