<ChangeLog project="SharpDevelop">
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/27/2006">Fixed SD2-917: Added project items not checked for illegal names</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/27/2006">Fixed SD2-1018: Nameing projects with especial characters makes them unable to run.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/27/2006">Fixed SD2-1020: Nameing project folders with ';' makes the solution unable to run.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/27/2006">Fixed SD2-996: C# assigned generic variables not converted correctly to VB.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/27/2006">Fixed SD2-1021: Alias for namespaces not converted correctly between C#&lt;--&gt;VB.NET for base types.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/27/2006">Fixed SD2-1027: #Develop closes while typeing VB 'ReDim' statement.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/27/2006">Fixed SD2-1029: Clean build after deleting GlobalAssemblyInfo.cs fails</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/27/2006">Applied forms designer assembly loading patch by Alex Prudkiy.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/27/2006">Add Notify Icon and Struct template by Justin Dearing.
The resource file template now creates .resx files by default.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/27/2006">Fix build error.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/27/2006">Fixed SD2-1023: SharpDevelop.exe.config bindingRedirect contains question marks
Update to new NSvn version (can now use Subversion 1.4 working copies)
Update StringResources.</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="08/24/2006">ColumnNodes in ReportExplorer can be DragDropped </Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/24/2006">Added a new Wix based installer for SharpDevelop. Improved performance of Wix files tree view, it now only adds child nodes when a node is expanded. Short filename generator now uses underscore instead of the tilde character preventing candle compilation warnings. User friendly names displayed in Wix files tree view for special folders (e.g. Program Files).</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="08/24/2006">Fixes from FxCop</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="08/24/2006">Remove unused Reports</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="08/24/2006">Update Examples Reports using StoredProcedures with Parameters (SQl Server + Northwind) added</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="08/24/2006">Worked on ParameterHandling for StoredProcedures (SQl Server)</Change>
  <Change author="Scott Ferrett" date="08/24/2006">#D core assemblies are only compatible with versions 1661 and later.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/24/2006">Update to Cecil 0.4.3.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/23/2006">SD2-1000: Deleting the ".." folder visible when the project contains incorrectly linked files deletes the whole parent directory</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/22/2006">Bugfix (Alex): pAppDomain can be null in NameChange callback</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="08/22/2006">minor changes to ensure that the user is prompted when an attempt it made to overwrite and existing local metadata file</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/22/2006">C# parser bug: fixed arrays in unsafe structs are now parsed correctly
XmlDoc.Load now does not throw an exception for invalid XML files.</Change>
  <Change author="Scott Ferrett" date="08/22/2006">Allow lists of unknown items to be retrieved from the property service.</Change>
  <Change author="Scott Ferrett" date="08/22/2006">Allow applications that use the SharpDevelop core to detect if the property service has been initialized, when there are no addins in the system.</Change>
  <Change author="Scott Ferrett" date="08/22/2006">You could not include a partial XML file in an .addin file using the "Include" element</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="08/21/2006">ServerBrowserTool now shows meta data for db objects such as Tables, Procedures etc. Loading of metadata from files is now invoked from right click menu for each connection rather than at start up. Beware will overwrite saved metadata if SaveAll invoked while 'empty' DbModelInfos are loaded.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/20/2006">Added a basic Wix directory, component and file editor - consists of a explorer-like tree view and property editor. Made the Wix project template more modular - separate files for the product, the user interface sequence, the component files and each dialog. Wix dialog designer can now find bitmap files defined in a different file to the dialog but part of the project.</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="08/15/2006">now has features: 1. can set/reset connection string for a connection, retrieve metadata, and save it, although it is not displayed in the UI. Beware! Metadata is currently unconstrained and consequently huge - a simple Oracle Express db is 67Mb of data in serialised xml form.</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="08/14/2006">If a Report has no Data, SharpReport prints a message, this message can be set within the ReportSettings, so no localisation is needed.</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="08/13/2006">More wip: ServerBrowserTool now loads and displays basic DbModelInfos using user's home dir</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="08/13/2006">Work on &lt;http://community.sharpdevelop.net/forums/thread/10479.aspx&gt; (Reports with StoredProcedures and Parameters), add a new Dialog for Parameter entry, did some refactoring to eleminate parts of SharpQuery</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="08/12/2006">Various fixes: can now add a ConnectionString to a DbModelInfo using the corresponding TreeNode, and SaveAll saves the content of each DbModelInfo to the user's home directory</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/10/2006">Show ToString() text in tooltip</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/10/2006">Moving functionality from NDebugger to Process - rewritten Debugger.AddIn to the process based model</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/10/2006">Currently selected xpath query result list item is highlighted in the XML editor. Fixed FileNotFound exception when running xpath queries on XMLSchema.xsd. Fixed exception that could occur when scrolling to the selected node when the XML had been removed.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/10/2006">Moving functionality from NDebugger to Process - Debugger.Core compiles again</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/10/2006">Moving functionality from NDebugger to Process - added ManagedCallbackSwitch

</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/10/2006">Moving functionality from NDebugger to Process - using ProcessEventArgs

</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/10/2006">Moving functionality from NDebugger to Process - rename debugger to process</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/09/2006">Store PauseSession per process</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="08/09/2006">Further mods to ServerBrowserTool and ConnectionStringDefinitionDialog to enable attaching connection strings to logical database connections - not currently working</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/09/2006">Added Goto Definition support for an XML schema. XML editor now supports navigation points. Xml query history now set to 20 items.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/09/2006">Added ExceptionThrown event; Some code moved to NDebugger.Pause</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="08/07/2006">additions to ServerBrowserTool and updates to ConnectionStringDefinitionDialog to modified connection string associated with a database connection</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/07/2006">Synchronous eval calls</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/07/2006">Changed the WiX project to use the OutputName MSBuild property as the .msi filename and not the project name to match how the WiX MSBuild tasks work.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/07/2006">Caching of variables</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="08/07/2006">Working on samples</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="08/07/2006">Fixes from FxCop</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/06/2006">Eval derives from Variable</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/06/2006">Fixed SD2-992: C# Interface public elements are converted to VB as Privates ones.
Fixed default visibility of inner types.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/06/2006">"throw new" now only shows types deriving from Exception.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/06/2006">Fixed SD2-964: Public VB structure variables are recognized as private ones.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/06/2006">Fixed SD2-968: C# to VB conversion error for generic structures.</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="08/06/2006">Work on ReportExplorer, fixes from FxCop</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/06/2006">Fixed SD2-971: Correct VB arrays declaration and redim-statements are recognized as code errors.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/06/2006">Add LineCounter AddIn to samples.</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="08/06/2006">More WIP: addition of DbModelInfos to cache and refresh of ServerBrowserTool</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/05/2006">Fixed code-completion bug (NullReferenceException) introduced in rev. 1661
</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/05/2006">Fix web reference unit tests by initializing the LanguageBindingService with dummy data.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/05/2006">Fixed code-completion unit tests.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/05/2006">Web references in Boo projects are now supported.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/05/2006">Added an XPath Query pad - can be used to run xpaths on the active XML document and highlights the resulting matches.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/05/2006">Put ICSharpCode.SharpDevelop.Dom in a separate assembly.
WorkbenchSingleton.SafeThreadCall is now a generic method to check that the types of the arguments match the parameter types expected by the delegate.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/05/2006">Fixed null reference exception that occurred if the WiX dialog designer was switched to when no WiX project was open.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/04/2006">Set Revision svn keyword; forgot to commit two files</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/04/2006">Created IMutable interface to propagate Changed event of variables</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="08/04/2006">More WIP - updates to DbModelInfo, DbModelInfoService and ServerBrowserTool</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/03/2006">Started getting of local variables for boo</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/03/2006">Added NewObjectEval; 
Removed some eval events</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="08/03/2006">Modify SharpReportAddin.csproj</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="08/03/2006">Delete unused FieldsExplorer/FieldsExplorer.cs</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="08/03/2006">Better usage for ReportExplorer</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/02/2006">Fixed SD2-960: Rename file from class view does not update project</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/02/2006">Fixed SD2-869: When opening a project with solution, ensure the solution contains the project</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/02/2006">The WiX controls sidetab now sets the hint path using the addinpath string parser property. Fixes the exception that occurred on opening the toolbox when SharpDevelop's working directory was not the bin folder.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/02/2006">Fixed SD2-963: Incorrect VB to C# convertion for public structure variables</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/02/2006">Fixed SD2-967: Buffer convertion from C# to VB throws exception if C# code contains the 'fixed' keyword.</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="08/01/2006">added prototype classes for various node types that will make up the Database part of the ServerBrowserTool</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="08/01/2006">some updates to addin file, DbModelInfoService and ServerBrowserTool</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/01/2006">Fixed SD2-904 by displaying an error message if a class contains multiple InitializeComponents methods.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/01/2006">Prevent fold markers from disappearing if they have no text (fixes SD2-977)</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/01/2006">File extensions that are to be opened in the XML Editor are now defined in the XmlEditor.addin file and not by the text editor library. This means that a user can add a new extension by editing the XmlEditor.addin file without needing to edit and recompile the text editor library.</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="08/01/2006">#region formatting, fixes</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/01/2006">Propagate errors from VariableCollection indexer by exception</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/01/2006">Fixed setting of breakpoints for multiple appdomains</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/01/2006">Fixed setting of breakpoints in methods with compiler generated code</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/31/2006">Add IconEditor AddIn (can currently only view icons, modifying them will be added later)
Supported icon formats:
- classic (AND mask + XOR mask)
- XP (.bmp with embedded alpha channel)
- Vista (Embedded .PNG files, high-resolution icons up to 256x256)
The viewer also supports all the quirks I could find in my icon collection - 32x31 icons, monochrome icons with transparency, icons where color depth in IconHeader is wrong.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/31/2006">Updated WixBinding - added a custom WiX project type (.wixproj) which uses MSBuild to create the installer, added a simple dialog designer, added a setup dialogs list pad, updated to WiX 2.0.4221. StringParser can now expand GUIDs. Added new DesignerSerializationService used by XmlDesignerLoader to fix SD2-599 - cut, copy and paste not working when designing XML forms.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/31/2006">Automatically create ICSharpCode.SharpDevelop.Sda.dll.config from app.template.config</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/31/2006">Fix file headers: set svn:keywords=Revision on all files; apply file header to all files; make all files UTF-8.</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="07/31/2006">Updated contributors list</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="07/30/2006">Minor change to DbModelInfoService</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="07/30/2006">More work in progress on DbModelInfo and ServerBrowserTool</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="07/30/2006">Added DbModelInfoFactory.cs</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/30/2006">Added some debugging info into debug tooltips</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/30/2006">Make Consolas the default font on Vista.
Allow runtime pad creation.
Ad SharpDevelopInteraction example to SdaUser.</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="07/29/2006">settled on DataSet to represent connection and model info. removed ConnectionInfo</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/29/2006">Add UpdateAssemblyInfo.exe.manifest - prevents UAC popups when compiling SharpDevelop on Vista</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="07/29/2006">corrected spelling of my name ;-)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/28/2006">Add ICSharpCode.SharpDevelop.Sda and SdaUser example application.</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="07/28/2006">Samples for IList as DataSource, EventLogger is a Report that shows dynamic use of images in a Report,ContributersList shows a couple of Contributers </Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="07/28/2006">Iamges can be set/changed at runtime</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="07/27/2006">More fixes from FxCop</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="07/27/2006">Work on Collections as DataSource. Fixed some stuff from FxCop</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="07/26/2006">work in progress - added more detail around connection, metadata and object view management</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/25/2006">Remove unnecessary usage of Assembly.GetEntryAssembly</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="07/24/2006">Fixed a problem with Fonts, make some changes from FxCop</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="07/24/2006">Update SharpReport Examples</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/22/2006">Implemented enum completion after "return".</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/22/2006">Fixed SD2-920: Refactoring menu options for enums contains invalid options</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/22/2006">When creating a property in VB, rename the field if it would conflict with the property name (fixes SD2-947)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/22/2006">Fixed some translation issues.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/21/2006">SD2-945: Typing a declaration of two or more variables in the same line (VB) throws exception</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/21/2006">Move files to match new namespace structure.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/21/2006">Improved NRefactory public API (moving classes to other namespaces etc.)</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="07/21/2006">Fixed Unbound printing for FormSheet Reports</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/21/2006">Fixed SD2-891: Content of VB 'With' statement not converted correctly to C#
Fixed SD2-894: Abstract properties declaration not converted correctly from VB to C#
Fixed SD2-895: VB 'Not' operator is not converted correctly to C#
Fixed SD2-901: VB 'Continue' statement not converted correctly from C#
Fixed SD2-902: C# 'break' statement not converted correctly to VB</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="07/21/2006">Move samples to SharpDevelop2.1</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/21/2006">Fixed SD2-930: VB exponential operator not converted to C#
Fixed SD2-879: Folding breaks with consecutive operators in VB code
Fixed SD2-906: Folding breaks on VB property declaration
Fixed SD2-921: Definitions in one line converted incorrectly from VB to C#
Fixed SD2-903: 'Using' statement not converted correctly from VB to C#
Fixed SD2-890: 'uint' type converted incorrectly from C# to VB
Fixed SD2-907: static method level variables are not translated from VB to C#</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="07/20/2006">uploaded a new version of my Help 2.0 register tool including its source</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/20/2006">Merged missing SharpReport resources from Corsavy.
Fixed some bugs in code analysis-AddIn.</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="07/19/2006">added addin file</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/19/2006">Add "Suppress message" command to FxCop warnings on the error list</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="07/19/2006">Added SharpDbTools project to the SharpDevelop.sln</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/19/2006">Fixed some FxCop warnings in NRefactory.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/19/2006">Fixed SD2-922: RegEx window not restoring its size after been maximized</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/17/2006">Added Debugger.BooInterpreter</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="07/17/2006">Fixed SD2-937</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="07/17/2006">Fixed SD2-939</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="07/17/2006">possible workaround to SD2-941.
i couldn't reproduce the problem illustrated in SD2-941, but instead this addresses the crash when BooBinding tries to reference FormsDesigner if the FormsDesigner.addin file does not exist.</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="07/17/2006">Fixed the following build errors for the SharpDevelop.Tests solution:
Main\Base\Test\Services_Navigation\NavigationServiceTestFixture.cs(115,52)
: error CS1026: ) expected
Main\Base\Test\Services_Navigation\NavigationServiceTestFixture.cs(128,55)
: error CS0117: 'ICSharpCode.Core.NavigationService' does not contain a definition for 'GetListOfPoints'
</Change>
  <Change author="Dickon Field" date="07/16/2006" />
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/16/2006">Allow AddIns to customize the MSBuild logger.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/16/2006">Implemented SD2-572: Enum autocomplete</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/16/2006">Implemented SD2-446: Support skipping method bodies in VB Lexer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/16/2006">NRefactory now preserves blank lines.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/16/2006">Work around MSBuild CopyToOutputDirectory bug.
Fixed NRefactory unit tests.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/16/2006">New feature: move class to file</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/15/2006">ObjectValue split into ObjectValue and ObjectValueClass; 
Variable submenus implemented in Debugger.Core</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/15/2006">NRefactory: use Location structure instead of System.Drawing.Point for source positions.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/15/2006">Boo.InterpreterAddIn now can host multiple interpreters</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/15/2006">Some FxCop suggestions to NRefactory.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/15/2006">Update to log4net 1.2.10.</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="07/15/2006">Fixed suggestions by FxCop for NavigationService; </Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/14/2006">Merged Corsavy r1517:1567 to trunk.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/12/2006">Search and Replace dialog buttons disabled if no find pattern entered. Search/replace keyboard shortcuts now switch between the search/replace tabs when the search and replace dialog has the focus.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/12/2006">SD2-918. Unit tests window - Run tests right click menu option available when no tests are loaded.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/12/2006">Added keyboard shortcut to open Code Coverage window. Added text editor right click and edit menu options to show/hide code coverage.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="07/12/2006">Help 2.0: more suggestions made by FxCop</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="07/11/2006">updated document headers NavigationService additions</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="07/11/2006">Added support for IViewContent navigation history (known in the Wiki as Code Navigation).  Basic documentation available in the XML comments for ICSharpCode.Core.NavigationService</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="07/11/2006">ToolBarSplitButton now supports disabling the button while leaving the dropdown enabled; addin files can now specify a disabledIcon for a ToolBarSplitButton's button.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/11/2006">Fixed forum-9740 (When renaming an item in a treeview and using the Del key, #D tries to delete the whole item)</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/10/2006">PersistentValue merged into Variable</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/10/2006">Initial code of boo console</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/09/2006">Completely rewritten variable life-time management and updating; 
Rewritten property evaluation</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="07/08/2006">Help 2.0: a few fixes and a first bunch of FxCop suggestions</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/07/2006">PersistentValue stored in Values - lifetime of Values increased</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/06/2006">Working on PersistentValue</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/06/2006">PersistentCorValue merged into PersistentValue</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/06/2006">All values are created in PersistentValue</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/06/2006">ICorDebugValue of Value stored in PersistentCorValue container 2 (missed file)</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/06/2006">ICorDebugValue of Value stored in PersistentCorValue container</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/06/2006">ValueGetter delegate wrapped in PersistentValue class</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/05/2006">Bugfix: Check function expiration in all callbacks with thread</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/05/2006">Fixed SD2-933: No debugger data tip when variable prefixed with "this"</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/05/2006">Fixed SD2-864: Exception when starting invalid application</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/05/2006">Fixed Forum-9220(cgraefe): Show error message for .NET Framework 1.0 programs</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/05/2006">Forum-8944(kama): Added hint for error 0x80131C30</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/04/2006">Fixed Forum-8847(asl): Breakpoints can be set within whole method</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/04/2006">Fixed Forum-8700(asl): Refactored stepping to increase performance (using StepOut for tracking again)</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/04/2006">Fixed Forum-8647(asl): Process post-break callbacks</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/04/2006">Fixed Forum-8646(asl): Release tracked COM objects synchronously</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/03/2006">Fixed Forum-8643(asl): Reset tracking stepper after evaluation</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/03/2006">Fixed Forum-8642(asl): Do not evaluate when native frame is on top of stack</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/03/2006">Fixed Forum-8640(asl): 'this' may not be available at native IP</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="07/02/2006">Help 2.0: fixed a filter loading problem in the Search panel; changed a few other things</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/29/2006">Added 'Find Next Selected' search menu option which will find the next occurrence of the selected text in the document.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="06/28/2006">Help 2.0: rewritten code for the controls to support empty/broken collections without getting errors</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="06/26/2006">Help 2.0: a lot of changes in the code</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/24/2006">Applied "Providing text editor tooltips using the AddInTree" patch by Christian Hornung.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="06/24/2006">Help 2.0: new config class used</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/24/2006">Support alternate new file dialogs (patch by Scott Ferrett)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/24/2006">Fixed build error introduced by merge.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/24/2006">Merged Corsavy r1470:1511 to trunk.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="06/24/2006">Help 2.0: made some changes in the Search pad and Config form code</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/24/2006">SD2-721. Can now delete files and folders from the project browser using the delete key.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/24/2006">SD2-856. When indenting xml that is not well formed SharpDevelop no longer displays an error message showing the XmlException.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/24/2006">SD2-843. When editing XML file with url dtd reference whilst having no network connection the WebException is now caught by the XML Editor.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="06/21/2006">Fixed SD2-846:Saving XSLT output to a file throws an invalid operation exception</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="06/21/2006">Fixed SD2-855:Attempting to create event handler for xml form terminates SharpDevelop</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="06/21/2006">Fixed SD2-845:Null reference exception when attempting to show tooltip for XSLT output</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="06/17/2006">fixed some flaws in the TOC and Index control</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="06/17/2006">catched an exception with invalid pointers (http://community.sharpdevelop.net/forums/thread/8728.aspx)</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="06/17/2006">new SharedAddin template for VBNet</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="06/17/2006">new SharedAddin template for VBNet</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/16/2006">Applied custom quick class browser patch by Robert Zaunere.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="06/16/2006">Fixed vb.net syntax coloring bug</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/10/2006">Merged Corsavy r1425:1470 to trunk.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="06/09/2006">new Shared Add-in template for creating add-ins for Office etc.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/06/2006">Prevent exception when Cecil doesn't report a return type for a member.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="06/03/2006">updated HtmlHelp2Options.cs a little bit</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="06/03/2006">updated WinFX samples for the WinFX CTP May 2006</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/28/2006">Update to new Cecil version, fixes exception when loading mixed-mode assemblies.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/27/2006">Merged Corsavy r1387:1425 to trunk.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/27/2006">Fixed bugs introduced in rev 1423.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/27/2006">Fixed SD2-815: Generic delegate throws null reference exception
Fixed SD2-819: Disabling code coverage and code analysis addin causes error on showing project properties</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/26/2006">Referenced assemblies are now loaded with Mono.Cecil.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/25/2006">Fixed unit tests.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/25/2006">Reduce usage of ProjectContentRegistry.Mscorlib - we'll support multiple mscorlib project contents later (compact framework, older .NET versions etc.)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/24/2006">Add NRefactory demo application.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/23/2006">Turned off overflow checks,Component Inspector error dialog now sends the user to the SharpDevelop bug reporting forum, and removed unused files.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/21/2006">Added Oakland Software's Component Inspector.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/07/2006">BooAdvancedHighlighter: only resolve references that in the visible part of the document</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/06/2006">Added support for advanced syntax highlighters.
Boo: Assignments that introduce new local variables are highlighted.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/06/2006">Add Rename command to refactoring menu.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/06/2006">New feature: Removed unused "using" statements.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/05/2006">Merged Corsavy r1333:1387 to trunk.</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="04/23/2006">recent changes to ToolBarDropDownButton are now compatible with previous usage, notably in the SearchAndReplace toolbar.
AddIn schema now updated to reflect recent addition to ToolbarItemDoozer; new ToolbarItem types are now available via code-completion in AddIn.xsd</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="04/23/2006">Applied patch by John Simons:
- resolves the flicker that appears in the last revision</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="04/23/2006">Applied patch by John Simons:
- adds 4 new ToolbarItem types:
  - TestBox -&gt; ToolBarTextBox
  - SplitButton -&gt; ToolBarSplitButton
  - Label -&gt; ToolBarLabel
  - Builder -&gt; ISubmenuBuilder
- also modifies the existing DropDownButton to support subitems like the menu does.

</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/22/2006">Serralongue now runs on x64 again (patched DockPanelSuite problem: http://sourceforge.net/tracker/index.php?func=detail&amp;aid=1438642&amp;group_id=110642&amp;atid=659401)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/22/2006">Merged Corsavy r1300:1333 to trunk.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/13/2006">Merged Corsavy r1251:1300 to trunk.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/13/2006">Implemented SD2-706: Opening single files in current SharpDevelop instance</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/03/2006">Applied Forms Designer patch by Robert Zaunere.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/03/2006">Default syntax highlighting strategy can be extended - patch by Robert Zaunere.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/03/2006">Class Browser now supports node builders (based on patch by Robert Zaunere)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/02/2006">Merged Corsavy r1227:1251 to trunk.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/01/2006">Fixed exception when typing Ctrl+Space in Boo Interpreter.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/22/2006">Worked on FxCop integration.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/20/2006">Implemented FxCop task.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/19/2006">Merge Corsavy r1208:1227 to trunk.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/11/2006">Add missing dependencies for NSvn.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/11/2006">Merged Corsavy r1195:1208 to trunk:
  Update to Boo 0.7.6.2160.
  Fixes SD2-495, SD2-719 and SD2-703.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/09/2006">Validating .xsd files now uses the XmlSchema class which returns better error information.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/04/2006">Merged Corsavy r1183:1195 to trunk:
Improved VB -&gt; C# converter.
Add Grouping (only one Column) to SharpReport
Fixed exception when opening a solution containing web projects.
Fixed SD2-711: Clear all bookmarks menu option selected when bookmarks pad not visible</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/04/2006">SubversionAddIn now shows commands in the project pad context menu; TortoiseSvn is used to display the dialogs.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/03/2006">Update to new NSvn build.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/01/2006">SD2-464.  Added projects and solutions options.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/28/2006">Add Code Analysis AddIn (can control which FxCop rules to run).
For some reason, FxCop is not being run inside SharpDevelop; but it is when running msbuild.exe from the command line.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/26/2006">Applied IntermediateOutputPath patch by Jeremy Brayton.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/26/2006">SD2-675 - Left/right keys should move the cursor when displaying the code completion window.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/26/2006">Merged Corsavy r1166:1183 to trunk:
Fixed SD2-695.  Unsetting a breakpoint when viewing an xml document no longer leaves red text behind.
Fixed SD2-693 - ToolstripContainer designer loading problem
Fixed SD2-700: Exception when selecting AddIn Manager About option
Fixed SD2-687: Cannot build entire solution after importing SharpDevelop 1.1 project
Fixed exception when loading a project when a referenced library was missing dependencies.
Fixed forum-5455: Importing old Visual Studio projects with non-ASCII characters in system encoding fails.
Fixed SD2-662, SD2-664 - Replace all inserting incorrect text or getting stuck in an infinite loop.
Fixed SD2-688: Selecting GAC list items in the Add Components dialog
Fixed SD2-676: Code completion for a class with many methods can be slow</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/25/2006">SD2-704.  The find next button is set to be the default button on the search and replace dialog.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/25/2006">Applied patch by John Simons: Closing an open file tab returns focus to the previously focused tab.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/23/2006">Conditions are now supported in the &lt;Runtime&gt; section of the .addin files. This allows choosing different assemblies based on properties like ${Platform} (Win32 or Win64).
The new &lt;DisableAddIn&gt; element can be used to disable AddIns completely based on conditions, e.g. when a platform is not supported at all.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/21/2006">PInvoke form now uses the .NET framework's built-in combo box auto-complete, instead of implementing its own.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/21/2006">Added support for NCover's attribute-based type exclusion (command line parameter //ea).  The attributes that will be used to exclude methods or classes can be set in the code coverage project options.  Excluded items will not be displayed in the code coverage pad.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/20/2006">Added format option to the XML menu which will format and indent the entire xml document.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/18/2006">Added extra display options for Code Coverage Pad.  Can now choose to show/hide the visit count list, optionally view the source code next to the coverage tree, or just display the tree on its own.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/18/2006">Merged Corsavy r1138:1166 to trunk.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/16/2006">Modified the MonoCompilerTask class (base class for all mono compiler tasks) so it uses Microsoft's ToolTask class to run the compiler instead of doing all the work itself.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/15/2006">VB.NET projects can now target Mono via the MonoBasic compiler.  All Mono compiler command lines now logged and can be seen when running MSBuild from the command prompt.  Added Gtk# project and file template for VB.NET.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/15/2006">Add quotation marks to batch files -&gt; fixes build if the SharpDevelop path contains a space</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/13/2006">VB.NET projects can now target different versions of Microsoft's .NET framework.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/13/2006">Apply our patches to the DockPanel Suite.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/13/2006">Use template file for SharpDevelop.exe.config to prevent Subversion conflicts.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/13/2006">Upgrade to DockPanel Suite 1.0.0.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/12/2006">Add Boo.InterpreterAddIn and SubversionAddIn.
Use separate directory for storing settings.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/12/2006">Update AssemblyInfo to version 2.1.</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="02/12/2006">Change log for Beta 2</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="02/12/2006">Modified the sample document for SharpReport. All images are now external to the document (all future documents should follow this guideline, and link to external PNGs instead of embedding images; allows for easier image reuse)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/12/2006">Update StringResources</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/12/2006">Add HtmlPreview and ImageViewer sample AddIns.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/12/2006">Add samples/ICSharpCode.Core.Demo and samples/NRefactoryExample.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/12/2006">Exclude all languages with more than 600 missing translations.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="02/12/2006">SD2-658: SharpDevelop Options Panel Template not up to date</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/12/2006">Applied patch by Christian Hornung: Forms designer resource loading</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/12/2006">Infer array literal context from context in FormsDesigner CodeDom converter.
Updated Boo.Lang.CodeDom.dll -&gt; fixes generation of array literals.</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="02/12/2006">Changed readme File to RTF, delete bin and bin/Debug</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="02/12/2006">SharpReport Exampels</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="02/12/2006">Small changes from FxCop, modifid ConnectionObject.cs</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="02/12/2006">Informational resources document updated</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="02/12/2006">Copyright updated</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="02/12/2006">Old documents deleted (format change)</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/11/2006">Ported all SharpDevelop 1.1 samples apart from the language binding sample.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/11/2006">Fixed bug: "Run Tests in Debugger" / "Run with NCover" / etc fail with warnings.
Fixed code-completion in anonymous methods when anonymous method was used as initializer in variable declaration.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/11/2006">Fixed BOO-653: Creating a new class without a file extension does not put the build action to compile.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/11/2006">Applied patch by Scott Ferret: Enhancement to Cut/Copy/Paste</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/11/2006">Fixed SD2-426: About box / Version info tab / Copy (the clipboard seems to be set correctly, we can ignore the ExternalException)
Fixed SD2-684: Cannot open a new form without saving it first.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/11/2006">Fixed bug: Line number of breakpoint did not change with code edits</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/10/2006">Fixed Forum-4943: Debugger says "Function has expired"</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/10/2006">Extended debugger test FunctionVariablesLifetime to check for "Function Expired" bug</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/10/2006">Removed unused merging functions from VariableCollection</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/10/2006">Fixed Forum-4946: error indenting single-line If-statements.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/09/2006">Rebuilt Bitmap resources so new SharpReport icons are accessible through the ResourceService.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="02/09/2006">patch from scott ferret: saving image resources with the correct extension</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="02/09/2006">applied path from scott ferrett correctly</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="02/08/2006">applied patch from scot ferrett</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/08/2006">The xml editor now keeps the existing document folds if the xml is no longer well formed.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/08/2006">Fixed Forum-5038: using "Go to line number" does not clear the selection.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/08/2006">Allow CodeCompletionDataProvider to specify the chars that are allowed to be entered while the code completion window is opened.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/08/2006">Fixed Forum-4952,5005 - Ignored errors when manipulating pdb files</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/08/2006">Fixed SD2-666: Code generation for EventHandler produces invalid code
Fixed SD2-589: Accessing disposed object on shutdown error logged</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/08/2006">Fixed SD2-680: Exception when deleting the *Designer.cs partial class file</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="02/08/2006">Better localisation of FieldsExplorer.cs, no dragging of Functions</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/07/2006">Fixed SD2-678.  Unit testing pad's stop toolbar button is now disabled after a test run has finished.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/07/2006">Signature suggested by Ingo Scholtes used for CreateDebuggingInterfaceFromVersion</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/07/2006">Fixed build error and Forum-4986.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/07/2006">Fixed SD2-580: Adding GAC reference to standard .NET assemblies adds full assembly name to project</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/07/2006">Fixed SD2-679.  Attempting to create a directory in the project browser containing invalid characters, such as a backslash, will display an error message.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="02/07/2006">load resoures when addin is inserted and enabled</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="02/07/2006">don't load resources if hintPath is null</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/07/2006">Moved ProcessRunner and associated classes out of the NAnt and Code Coverage addin and into ICSharpCode.SharpDevelop (Base).</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="02/07/2006">Fixing Issue SD2-669 from Matt Ward</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="02/07/2006">Fixing Issue SD2-688 from Matt Ward</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/07/2006">Console applications run from debug build of #D have their own console</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="02/07/2006">bitmap/string resources can now be registered in *.addin files using the tags &lt;BitmapResources&gt; and &lt;StringResources&gt;</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/07/2006">Implemented SD2-663 - you can copy values from tooltips to clipborad; 
Values of properties can not be edited</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/07/2006">Implemented SD2-546: Breakpoints that will not be hit should have different icon; 
Reworked breakpoint synchronization.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/07/2006">Improved speed of expanding tree nodes in code coverage tree view - child nodes added only when the node is expanded via the ExtTreeNode.Initialize method.  Classes with no namespace are now added to the tree view without a parent namespace node.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/06/2006">Renaming in Breakpoint class. Added WillBeHit property to BreakpointBookmark.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/06/2006">Fixed SD2-674: Invalid indentation used by "override" code generator.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/06/2006">Fixed SD2-649: Breakpoint within anonymous delegate method causes COMException</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/06/2006">Fixed some NRefactory bugs, added NRefactory unit tests.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/06/2006">Fixed SD2-633: Trying to debug a non .NET executable throws an exception</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="02/06/2006">Applied patch by John Simons: Closing an open file tab returns focus to the previously focused tab.  Patch edited slightly to use generics &amp; follow DockPane.cs naming conventions.</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="02/06/2006">"Save all currently open buffers" option added to OpenFileTab/ContextMenu</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/06/2006">Sort ExtTreeView only when expanding a node for the first time instead of every time a node is expanded.
OverrideMethodsCodeGenerator now shows methods from base classes when the base class definition is in another part of the class.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/05/2006">Fixed SD2-670: Second form resource added if design view switched to from designer partial class</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/05/2006">Fixed SD2-673: Opening invalid projects raises exception</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/05/2006">Modified code coverage project guid so SharpDevelop.Tests solution now works.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/05/2006">Added missing string resources for Code Coverage addin.</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="02/05/2006">Further refactoring of ReportGenerator, new Exception MissingModelException.cs added</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/05/2006">Fixed unit tests.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/05/2006">Switch from MbUnit to NUnit:
Fixes SD2-621 (ExpectedException test failure not added to error list), SD2-408 (Add "Run Test" to member bookmark), SD2-618 (Run test fixture in console with debugger shows no output).</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/05/2006">Items that have zero code coverage are now displayed in grey in the tree view.  Added tests and code to parse NUnit xml output files - not currently used.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/05/2006">Output text line parser now successfully parses NUnit output containing a carriage return character.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/05/2006">When a tree node in the ExtTreeView is selected, but the control does not currently have the focus, the node's text colour is set to ControlText and not the node's ForeColor.  This makes the ExtTreeView consistent with the .NET framework TreeView.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/04/2006">Fixed SD2-672: Applications using DynamicProxy cannot be debugged</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/03/2006">BreakPointsPad derives from BookmarksPad. Implements: 
SD2-608: Cannot remove breakpoints via breakpoint pad; 
SD2-609: Cannot go to source code line from breakpoint pad; 
SD2-610: Saved breakpoints should be displayed in breakpoint pad on opening a solution</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/03/2006">Fixed Forums-3382,3489,3575: Attempt to display property of property crashed the debugger</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/03/2006">Fixed SD2-638: Crash when closing console window during debugging; 
Added debugger test: DebuggeeKilled

</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/02/2006">Fixed SD2-637: Cannot expand array in debugger tree view; 
Fixed SD2-612: Debugger exception generated when viewing XmlNamespaceManager members</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="02/02/2006">Small changes in ReportGenerator and better handling of IDisposable</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/02/2006">Added debugger test: ArrayValue</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/01/2006">Add JScriptGlobals by John Simons: HtmlHelp settings (e.g. language filter) are now persisted.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="01/31/2006">Added code coverage addin - supports NCover.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/31/2006">Fixed exception when adding solution folder.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/30/2006">Patch by Scott Ferrett: List of project file extensions to open when the file was specified on the command line was hardcoded to csproj,vbproj,booproj; now it can be extended using the AddIn tree.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/30/2006">Fixed SD2-661: Project browser cannot be navigated with keyboard
Fixed SD2-578: Changing the "Name" property in the designer does not change the form class name</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="01/30/2006">FieldsExplorer is invisible until SharpReport run's and update themself from SharpReportView
at start and when View's changed</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="01/30/2006">Fixed another possible NullReferenceException in recent changes to the project browser.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/29/2006">Fixed SD2-640: Add existing form to project does not add .resx file</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/29/2006">Applied forms designer patch by Christian Hornung: use the MenuCommandService implementation from the .NET framework.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/29/2006">Fixed SD2-639: Renaming a form should rename the resource file</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/29/2006">Fixed SD2-654: Get file types to register from AddIn tree.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/28/2006">Fixed SD2-656: Show tab order menu option should indicate current state</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/28/2006">Fixed SD2-484: Designer verbs not displayed in forms designer</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/28/2006">Fixed SD2-652: Code completion for form component with modifier set to public
Fixed SD2-659: No code completion for newly added components to a partial form class</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/28/2006">Fixed SD2-653: Design tab missing for new form added to project</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/28/2006">Use default help namespace when help2environment.xml is empty.</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="01/28/2006">Change delegates to EventHandler&lt;T&gt;</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="01/27/2006">Fixes from FxCop</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/27/2006">Fixed exception when renaming project while project options are opened.</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="01/27/2006">Folder's are set correctly from ReportWizard</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/25/2006">Fixed path to ngen.
${ProductName} now can be used as reference to the name of the product using ICSharpCode.Core.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/25/2006">PostInstallTasks now calls ngen for SharpDevelop.exe (and its dependencies).</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="01/25/2006">More fixes from FxCop</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="01/24/2006">Applied some rules from FxCop</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="01/23/2006">removed namespace declartions and imports from code</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/23/2006">The Boo forms designer now supports partial classes.
VB and Boo templates now use partial classes for the forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="01/23/2006">added subcategory definitions to vb.net tempates; added singleton and addin templates</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="01/23/2006">Grouped code according to interface implementations and added #region wrappers to identify them.
No change to code or functionality.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/23/2006">Fixed SD2-651: Opening a single file displays error message</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/23/2006">Fixed SD2-650: Find References error with single file open</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="01/23/2006">Fixed null reference exception in project browser if the last selected file is null.</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="01/23/2006">Forgot to clean ReportModel.cs</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="01/23/2006">Cleanup</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="01/23/2006">Improved ProjectBrowser's ability to track the selected file.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/22/2006">Add some strings to the translation database.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/22/2006">Include SharpReport in default build.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/22/2006">C# form template now uses partial classes. File templates now can use the "DependentUpon" attribute.</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="01/21/2006">Fixed small bug introduced by recent changes that entered search results twice for FindAll searches.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/21/2006">I forgot to check in some files...</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/21/2006">Fixed SD2-579: Design tab not always available for partial class forms (patch by Christian Hornung)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/21/2006">C# &lt;-&gt; VB converter now converts P/Invoke declarations.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/20/2006">Fixed C# lexer: double-quote in verbatim string parsed incorrectly</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/20/2006">Put more strings into the translation database.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="01/20/2006">Toolbox provider no longer refreshes the project browser pad since new references are added by the project browser itself.  This also fixes a null reference exception that was occuring when the project browser instance was accessed when the pad had not been created.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/20/2006">Fixed NRefactory bugs regarding "else if"-statements.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/20/2006">Fixed copy-paste into RTF editors when text contained backslash.</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="01/20/2006">Fixed endless loop for nonsorted Reports, implement a basic checking of CommandText, (check for 'Update' and 'Delete')</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="01/20/2006">Recent search results now show in most-recently-displayed-first order.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/19/2006">Added some strings to the translation database.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/19/2006">Fixed C# parser bug: cast followed by anonymous method.
Added "StringResourceToolAddIn" to src/Tools: little AddIn that helps adding resources to our internal translation database.</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="01/19/2006">Remove RunSharpReport.cs, Extract some Commands for SharpReportView and FieldsExplorer</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/19/2006">Removed Visual Styles workaround that is not needed on .NET 2.0 anymore. This fixes the background color of radio buttons in group boxes when WinXP is used but Visual Styles are disabled.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/18/2006">Project converter now converts project settings.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="01/18/2006">User is now prompted for discovery credentials when adding or refreshing a web reference if the server returns a Http status of 401 (Unauthorised).  Tested with basic and NT authentication.</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="01/17/2006">Add FileTemplate for Sharpreport</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="01/17/2006">Changed handling of Report Preview</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="01/17/2006">Modified DatabaseConnections</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/16/2006">Added SharpReport</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="01/16/2006">SearchResultPanel's 'Select Search Mode' drop-down menu is now generated dynamically from the SearchResultPanelViewMode enum.
The drop-down menu now shows which mode is currently selected by setting &amp; updating the ToolStripMenuItem.Checked property of each menu entry.</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="01/16/2006">SearchReplaceInFilesManager.ShowSearchResults now calls OnSearchAllFinished to log the results in the 'Show last searches' menu.

Results of RefactoringService features like FindReferences &amp; FindDerivedClasses are now stored &amp; accessible through this menu.
</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="01/16/2006">Change in SharpQuery.addin</Change>
  <Change author="Peter Forstmeier" date="01/16/2006">Small change in Collections.cs</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="01/16/2006">Changed file names of setup scripts</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/15/2006">Fixed exception in dynamic help pad when language of current project was unknown (e.g. project file not found)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/15/2006">Added SharpQuery.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/15/2006">Fixed project converter bugs.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/15/2006">Fixed NullReferenceException when converting C# statements like "if (a != null) b.c();"</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="01/14/2006">File and project template categories can now specify a sort order if required.  Defaults to sorting by category name.  Updated string resources for new templates.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/14/2006">Fixed exception on startup because the splash screen was initialized too early in release builds (creating forms in a static constructor is not a good idea).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/14/2006">Added project converter (C# &lt;-&gt; VB -&gt; Boo). Project settings are currently not converted.
Replaced most ToLower() and ToUpper() calls with ToLowerInvariant() and ToUpperInvariant(), or with string.Equals(, StringComparison.OrdinalIgnoreCase). This fixes file name comparisons in cultures with different ToLower/ToUpper rules.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/12/2006">Applied patch by Alex Prudkiy: fixes loading the forms designer when the file contains multiple classes.
Adjusted AssemblyInfo for 2006.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="01/11/2006">Project and file templates now support subcategories.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="01/10/2006">Revert change made to ProjectContentRegistry back to revision 983.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="01/10/2006">Reset accidentally modified assembly info version numbers.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="01/09/2006">Added support for Mono's GAC.  Added Gtk# and Glade# project templates.  Project templates can now clear any imports added by default.  Improved code completion for Mono GAC assemblies with dependencies.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/09/2006">Fixed code completion for global methods.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/09/2006">Fixed SD2-625: Cannot add solution items to the solution</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/08/2006">Fixed SD2-644: Exception when selecting text</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/08/2006">Added AbstractAstTransformer, using it now for the code converter. This should fix problem for certain statement combinations.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/08/2006">Forms designer is now reloading assemblies when required (based on patch by Alex Prudkiy).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/07/2006">delete directories Subversion didn't delete me on the first try</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/07/2006">Revert two forms designer files that shouldn't be committed...</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/07/2006">Added generator application to generate the NRefactory AST.
This will allow us to automatically generate the IAstVisitor and a future AstTransformer and we don't have to worry about forgetting some AST nodes.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/07/2006">Fixed VB output visitor: Named attribute arguments</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/06/2006">Update to NUnit 2.2.5.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/06/2006">Fixed Visual Basic operator precedence and added unit tests for operator precedence.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/06/2006">Fixed SD2-636: NRefactory -&gt; CodeDom converter might not work on first try.
Applied assembly loading patch by Alex Prudkiy.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/05/2006">Fixed problem introduces in last revision.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/05/2006">Fixed problem with highlighting strategy ("default" words had explicit background info set, which caused problems with the CustomLineManager)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/05/2006">Fixed bug converting AddHandler statements to C#.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/05/2006">Enable using PropertyGroups in the project templates. Updated ComplexExample, it should now demonstrate all project template features.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/05/2006">Fixed exception when trying to delete a MarshalByValueComponent (like DataSet) using the keyboard.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/04/2006">Fixed SD2-635: Code completion does not work for VB array access.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/04/2006">Overworked form designer assembly loading a bit. Showing the custom components in the tools pad no longer causes the assembly to be loaded, it is loaded only when the component in the toolbox is activated.
TypeResolutionService now searches for types using the code completion cache and loads the correct assembly when it is required by the designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/04/2006">Fixed SD2-632: Ctrl+Space "preselection" does not work.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="01/03/2006">Fixed typo - use MessageService.ShowError instead of non-existent MessageService.Show method.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/03/2006">Implemented right-to-left mirroring for dialogs and the main menu.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/02/2006">Fixed StackOverflow when showing project options for project stored on a remote network location.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/02/2006">Improved C# &lt;-&gt; VB conversion.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/31/2005">Fixed SD2-629: VBNetForeachLoopVariableTest.
Fixed some Boo code completion bugs.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="12/31/2005">Fixed SD2-626.  FileNode in the project browser now has its filename updated when its parent folder is renamed.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="12/30/2005">Fixed SD2-628 - Can now design unsaved files when a project is currently open.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="12/30/2005">Added support for web references.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/30/2005">Fixed SD2-511: Code completion in inserted line.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/30/2005">Fixed SD2-627: Debugger locking output exe on selecting debug | run.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/29/2005">Fixed SD2-463: Visibility of undocked panels.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/29/2005">Fixed SD2-459: Project scout viewstate not remembered.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/29/2005">Fixed SD2-436: Code Autogeneration. (code is now inserted at cursor position again)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/29/2005">Fixed SD2-613: Renaming a solution generates a Not Implemented exception.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/29/2005">Fixed SD2-624: "Configure Sidebar" not shown when right-clicking on the tools pad.
Add "OK" and "Cancel" buttons to CodeGenerationForm.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="12/28/2005">allow sorting of GAC panel</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/27/2005">Fixed BOO-628 - Alt+Ins code generation only works for C# and VB.
Alt+Ins code generators now use ICSharpCode.SharpDevelop.Refactoring.CodeGenerator.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/27/2005">Fixed VB interface implementation code generator.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/27/2005">Fixed BOO-589: Tooltip information fails when a property is named after a type</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/27/2005">Fixed BOO-613: Exception thrown when double clicking on '"' at the end of the document.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/26/2005">Fixed SD2-622 (Project folder name ending with backslash displayed incorrectly in project browser).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/26/2005">Use callback method for MSBuildEngine instead of Application.DoEvents() loop. Probably fixes SD2-619.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/26/2005">Fixed bug in the AddInManager when using "@Filename" version numbers.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/26/2005">Fixed possible StackOverflowException in pad creation.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/26/2005">Fixed parser crash on incomplete ReDimStatement.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="12/24/2005">When checking the project's references, after a control has been dropped onto a form in the designer, the code now ensures that the referenced assembly exists before trying to retrieve the assembly name.  If it does not exist the code tries the GAC.  This handles the case where the HintPath has been set to a folder which does not exist.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/23/2005">Fixed C#&lt;-&gt;VB conversion of #if preprocessing directives.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/22/2005">Fixed VB lexer crash when "&amp;H" was not followed by a number.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/22/2005">Fixed AltGr-shortcut bug. (AltGr+E now inserts the '€' sign instead of showing the exceptions pad).</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/22/2005">Last out parameter used as return value in CorDebugger wrapper; Methods starting with Get or Is converted to properties</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/21/2005">Fixed NullReferenceException when converting fields without initializer from C# to Boo.</Change>
  <Change author="David Alpert" date="12/21/2005">Refactored the AbstractMenuCommands in BuildCommands.cs</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/20/2005">CorDebugger wrapper used by the debugger</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="12/20/2005">worked on vb.net output vistitor: operator declarations</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/20/2005">Added wrappers for CorDebug</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/20/2005">Added WrapperGenerator</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/20/2005">Now MSBuild property $(SolutionDir) is available when compiling single projects.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="12/20/2005">Ported PInvoke addin from SharpDevelop 1.1</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/19/2005">Reset assembly info version number (see doc\technotes\Versioning.html for details)</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="12/19/2005">Beta 1 preparations</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/19/2005">Translations update.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/19/2005">Applied form designer assembly loading patch by Alex Prudkiy.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/18/2005">Changed license in about dialog to LGPL.</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="12/18/2005">Official license change from GPL to LGPL</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/18/2005">Changed splash screen.</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="12/18/2005">Forum link updated</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/18/2005">Disable SubversionAddIn (it won't ship with SharpDevelop 2.0).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/18/2005">Change file header.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/18/2005">Display name of AddIns: "Subversion AddIn" instead of "ICSharpCode.Svn"</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/18/2005">Use IntPtr instead of int in SendMessage P/Invoke declaration.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/18/2005">Fixed SD2-519: Project options panel can be opened multiple times for the same project.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/18/2005">Fixed SD2-593: Forms Designer events page not initially visible.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/18/2005">Fixed SD2-607: Null Reference exception on closing form designer.
Applied text editor IME patch by Shinsaku Nakagawa and form designer unloading patch by Christian Hornung.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/17/2005">Fixed SD2-574: tooltip delay (using system setting for MouseHoverTime)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/17/2005">Fixed small lexer problem.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/17/2005">Improved C# lexer performance.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/17/2005">Expressions with dot resolved properly in debugger tooltip</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/17/2005">Fixed SD2-584: .proj MSBuild files in solutions are shown as unknown project type.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/17/2005">Fixed SD2-606: Scrolling search window to the left corrupts text</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/17/2005">Fixed SD2-549: Scrolling split window after expanding a region</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/17/2005">Fixed SD2-603: Renaming a project in the project browser generates a not implement exception</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/16/2005">Events unregistered when debugger tooltip is closed</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/16/2005">Added Shown and Hidden events to DynamicListRow.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/16/2005">Fixed SD2-573: Editing menu item text in place</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/16/2005">Update language resources.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/16/2005">Fixed bug in C# to VB converter: AddEventHandler statements were not converted correctly.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/16/2005">Fixed SD2-586: Debugger not going to source code line from callstack view</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="12/16/2005">Help 2.0: small changes in the Dynamic Help browser scripting</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/15/2005">Fixed solution configuration -&gt; project configuration mapping.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/15/2005">Added debugger test: SetIP</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/15/2005">Allow changing the active solution configuration in the build menu.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/15/2005">Ported Fidalgo rev. 2115 (Ivo Kovacka): fixed some minor problems where object were staying in memory (missing dispose calls, event handlers not being deregistered).</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/14/2005">Debugger handles optimized code more gracefully</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/14/2005">Debugger.Eval rewritten to hold its state in one enum</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/13/2005">Private/static variables separated in debugger tooltips</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/13/2005">Fixed bug: SessionID was not updated between evals; Added test for it</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/13/2005">Fixed StackOverflowException and endless loop when classes had cyclic inheritance. Fixed the VB expression finder for "MethodCall().MethodCall()", added unit tests for the expression finder.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/13/2005">Added debugger test: PropertyVariableForm</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/13/2005">Fixed bug: 'this' is now passed to property eval as reference</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/13/2005">Added debugger test: PropertyVariable</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="12/13/2005">Fixed SD2-602 - Adding a COM reference generates a FileLoadException.  The ReferenceProjectItem was trying to determine the assembly name for the COM reference causing the exception.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/12/2005">Fixed bug: Base class was not accessible after stepping</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/12/2005">Added debugger test: ObjectValue</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/12/2005">Property evaluation code moved to ObjectValue</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/12/2005">Fixed SD2-595: Replace in files must use same Encoding detection as text editor</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/12/2005">Worked on variable updating; Properties in debugger tooltips</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/11/2005">ToString disabled; Property evaluation automatically started on demand</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/11/2005">Fixed SD2-525: Changing the output Window font changes the text editor window font.
Fixed SD2-526: Output Window Word Wrap does nothing.
Improved performance of output window and error list when there are many errors/warnings. (previously 3000 warnings caused the SharpDevelop to freeze for 30 seconds and then crash with an OutOfMemoryException, consuming 2 GB of memory; now the speed is much better and the memory usage is fixed)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/11/2005">Fixed SD2-570: When moving or copying InProject folders, their children get excluded from the project.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/11/2005">Fixed SD2-569: Wrong file name used for new Link items.
Fixed text editor crash when editing files containing very long words (e.g. 100 KB base64-data in a single line in an XML file).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/10/2005">Fixed SD2-597: No code completion after "new".</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/10/2005">Fixed SD2-600 (Can't convert for loop). VB parser now accepts zero as lower array bound.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/10/2005">Added debugger test: FunctionVariablesLifetime; 
Fixed function so that expired variables do not throw exceptions</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/10/2005">Update to NDoc 1.3.1-v11 from http://jonas.lagerblad.com/blog/?p=4 (unofficial version that works with .NET 2.0)
Now NDoc can be started with the command "Project &gt; Build documentation with NDoc".</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/10/2005">Added debugger test: FunctionLifetime</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/10/2005">Applied form designer patch by Christian Hornung:
- designer no longer rewrites fields of all parts in the designer file
- type names in non-designer parts are now correctly fixed to fully qualified type names
- designer no longer overwrites the wrong code region in the designer file
- when double-clicking an event which is defined in a different file, that file is now opened instead of a new (duplicate) method being created
- the design tab is now also shown if the System.Windows.Forms.Form base type is specified in the designer file, but not in the currently open file</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/10/2005">Added debugger test: FunctionLocalVariables</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/10/2005">Added debugger test: FunctionArgumentVariables</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/10/2005">Added debugger test: Callstack</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/10/2005">Added debugger test: Stepping</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/10/2005">Walkaround for pdb locking, added test for it</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/09/2005">Added debugger tests: Break, Symbols</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/08/2005">Fixed project reference to FormsDesigner.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/08/2005">Rename forms designer directory.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/08/2005">Move FormDesigner/Project/Src/FormDesigner/* to FormDesigner/Project/Src/*</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/08/2005">Move FormDesigner/Project/Src/FormDesigner/* to FormDesigner/Project/Src/*</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/08/2005">Rewriten MTA2STA so that it can be controlled more in MTA and tests</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/08/2005">Rename FormDesigner to FormsDesigner.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/08/2005">Improved C# -&gt; Boo converter.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/08/2005">SD2-592: Exception thrown when trying to copy a file</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/07/2005">Fixed SD2-466: Tools panel doesn't work in autohide mode</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/07/2005">Debugger tests pre-compiled</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/07/2005">Added two debugger tests</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="12/07/2005">Fixed SD2-598. Added ComponentSerializationService to XmlDesignerLoader to enable undo/redo when designing xml forms.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/07/2005">Fixed debugger test</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/07/2005">Misuse of delegate</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/06/2005">Lazy getting of object values</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/06/2005">Disabled failing debugger test.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/06/2005">Work around MSBuild bug: log4net.dll is not copied to the unit test output directory (and copying some other libraries just in case...)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/06/2005">Work around MSBuild bug: ICSharpCode.SharpDevelop.dll is not copied to the unit test output directory.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/06/2005">Lazy getting of property values</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/06/2005">NAntAddIn unit tests now don't need a hard-coded path in the config file.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/06/2005">Set output directory of unit test projects to bin\UnitTests</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/06/2005">Implemented designing forms and controls with Visual Inheritance (based on patch from Alex Prudkiy)</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="12/06/2005">Html Export menu option no longer gets disabled after being selected once.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/06/2005">Lazy getting refactored. Started lazy getting of properties</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/06/2005">Removed MessageBoxBuilder addin.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/06/2005">Use project references to NUnit.Framework instead of GAC references (NUnit isn't in the GAC on the build server).</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="12/06/2005">Fixed typos in VB.Net file templates.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/06/2005">Lazy getting of array values</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/05/2005">Lazy getting of function arguments and local variables</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/05/2005">Fixed enumerations with base type in VB output visitor.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/05/2005">Used constructor instead of Variable.CreateVariable</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/05/2005">Getting of function variable made lazy</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/05/2005">Debugger.Function valid as long as possible</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/03/2005">Fixed selection bug after double-clicking on a word (based on patch by 'ctlajoie').</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/03/2005">VariableFactory meged into Variable. ValueFactory merged into Value.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/02/2005">Some validity checking in debugger. Removed MagicValue and UnknownValue.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/02/2005">MTA2STA uses MethodInvoker delegate</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/02/2005">Rewritten Debugger.ManagedCallbackProxy</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="12/02/2005">Moved C++ and WiX templates to the (disabled) AddIn projects. (SD2-566)</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="12/02/2005">Rewritten Debugger.MTA2STA</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/30/2005">SD2-582: Solution file incorrect after adding a second project</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/30/2005">Fixed SD2-577: System.ArgumentException: Value does not fall within the expected range</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/30/2005">Fixed SD2-585: DataGridView does not appear in Tools | Data tab</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/29/2005">Add documentation about AddInManager.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/29/2005">Added context menu to AddInManager, put strings into translation database. Chloë (GeneralWizardBackground.png) now uses alpha transparency and looks great in different color profiles.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/28/2005">Fixed SD2-590: Form Designer does not show child controls of panel</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/27/2005">Improved AddInManager (updating AddIns now works correctly).
Form Designer now no longer rewrites fields without modifier, patch by Christian Hornung.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="11/27/2005">added icons for the debugger pads. they are not perfect but at lease distinctable.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/27/2005">Applied form designer field declaration patch by Christian Hornung.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/27/2005">Added support for installing and uninstalling user AddIns.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/27/2005">Implemented adding and removing external AddIns.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/26/2005">Check dependencies when enabling/disabling AddIns.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/26/2005">Add simple AddIn manager that can enable and disable AddIns.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/26/2005">Fixed SD2-587.  Windows forms component sidebars recreated if they do not exist when switching to an already opened forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/26/2005">Fixed SD2-588.  Type resolution service no longer returns types from the Microsoft.VSDesigner assembly.  This stops the forms designer from using Microsoft's data adapter designers.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/26/2005">Added workaround for TreeView bug when drawing selected nodes when the treeview does not have focus.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/26/2005">Now AddIns are loaded from three locations:
- ApplicationBase\AddIns
- ConfigDirectory\AddIns
- locations defined in ConfigDirectory\AddIns.xml</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/25/2005">Update to Boo 0.7.5, added support for partial classes to the Boo AddIn.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/25/2005">Patch by Scott Ferrett: Match whole word now accepts any non-letter-or-digit character as word bound, fixed exception when searching in "whole project" or "whole solution" and the project contained an open .resources file.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/25/2005">Use ToolStripManager.Renderer instead of MenuService.Renderer. Use ProfessionalRenderer+SystemColorTable instead of SystemRenderer.
The "CoreStartup" class now helps starting up the core and enables the core user to change the location of the properties file and some other core settings.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/25/2005">Fixed code completion in WithStatements.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/25/2005">Removed addin dependency from Forms Designer addin stopping it from being loaded on startup.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/25/2005">GAC references displayed using short names in project browser and class browser.  Extra GAC information displayed in property pad.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/24/2005">Show new AddIn properties in the AddInScout.
Fixed C# ExpressionFinder bug: identifiers were resolved as type names when they were in front of a keyword like 'in' or 'as'.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/24/2005">Fixed code completion for project references.
Added support for AddIn dependencies and conflicts to ICSharpCode.Core.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/24/2005">Fixed SD2-515.  Project or assembly reference added to the project when a custom component from the toolbox is added to a form.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/24/2005">Code now ensures that the Forms Designer UndoEngine has been created before checking that the undo/redo menu options should be enabled.</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="11/23/2005">SXW converted RTF; pending review by authors</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/23/2005">Set the DesignerSerializationVisibility to hidden for the TextEditorControlBase properties Document and TextEditorProperties.  This prevents the forms designer from generating code that cannot be compiled when the text editor control is added to a form at design time.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/23/2005">Applied Christian Hornung's fix for SD2-562.  The ViewContents are notified of deselection prior to the workspace layout being changed.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="11/23/2005">add MSBuildFile.cs for the last update 787</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="11/23/2005">updating repository to avoid the build bug (is no one responsible for this?)</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="11/22/2005">applied patch from Scott Ferrett: Support for % in itmes in MSBuild files</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="11/22/2005">some little updates and fixes</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/21/2005">Read unknown project items from MSBuild files, allow project to override creation of project items (patch by Scott Ferrett).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/20/2005">Fixed moving linked files in the project pad and other minor bugs.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/20/2005">Fixed SD2-462.  Undo/redo now working in the Forms Designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="11/20/2005">updated WinFX templates for the WinFX Runtime Components November 2005 CTP</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/20/2005">Fixed exception when loading referenced assembly using Reflection when a type parameter constraint on a method referenced another type parameter from the same method.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/20/2005">Fixed a few minor bugs.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/19/2005">ToString() evaluated in local variables pad</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/19/2005">ErrorListPad now uses TaskView (patch by David Alpert). Renamed ErrorList to ErrorListPad and OpenTaskView to TaskListPad.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/19/2005">Fixed SD2-564: Code always generated for c#.
Fixed VB parser bug ("Dim lDrives() As DriveInfo")</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/19/2005">Eval exceptions are handled</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/19/2005">Fixed some bugs in the project browser (Solution Folders and Solution Items)</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/19/2005">Form designer disposes the design surface without using BeginInvoke if the FormDesignerViewContent is being disposed.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/19/2005">Fixed some bugs regarding missing files and folders in the project browser.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/19/2005">Fixed SD2-565.  Cutting and pasting a file into its original directory no longer deletes the file.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/19/2005">Fixed SD2-551: Project view not always synchronising the current document</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/19/2005">Properties shown in local variables pad and debugger tooltip</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/18/2005">Numbers can be set using debugger tooltip</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/18/2005">Improved sorting of TaskList (patch by David Alpert)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/18/2005">Fixed NullReferenceException in DynamicHelpPad. Updated layout configuration to hide DynamicHelpPad by default.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/18/2005">Fixed some bugs in NRefactory.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/18/2005">Fixed SD2-561: Running a single file causes unhandled exception</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/18/2005">The Boo AddIn now supports code completion for generics. The C# -&gt; Boo converter now supports converting generic type references.
NRefactory now uses CastExpression for all cast types ("DirectCast", "CType", "TryCast"). TypeOfIsExpression now used by C# instead of BinaryOperatorType.TypeTest.
Updated to new Boo version that supports parsing and writing generic type references.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="11/17/2005">changed the call of the dialog and its Dispose() method a little bit</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="11/17/2005">IME patch from Shinsaku Nakagawa</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/16/2005">Fixed SD2-555.  Forms designer automatically reloads if the language property is changed.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/16/2005">Fixed SD2-556: Resx not being added to project</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="11/16/2005">SD2-532: revamped html export; made progress bar access threadsafe</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/15/2005">Added patch by Christian Hornung.  DesignerResourceService now complies with the SDK documentation and serves resource readers/writers at any time in any order.  Localised resources now saved correctly.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/15/2005">Added icons to debugger tooltips</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/15/2005">Variables in Local Variables pad are expandable again.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/15/2005">Debugger SubVariables property moved from Value to Variable.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/15/2005">Worked on Debugger.VariableCollection. Started redesign of local variables pad.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/14/2005">SharpDevelopMain.RunApplication() does not eat all exceptions</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/14/2005">Added Debugger.Variable</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/14/2005">Applied "Sortable OpenTaskView pad" patch from David Alpert.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/14/2005">Fixed VB lexer crash on empty char literals.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/13/2005">Fixed SD2-559: Jagged arrays don't parse</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="11/13/2005">correct comment prefix</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="11/13/2005">xml comment insertion and completition for vb.net</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/13/2005">Fixed SD2-558 (Override as variable name) and the first half of SD2-559 (Jagged arrays don't parse)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/13/2005">Fixed SD2-560: Interface implementation generator messes up arrays</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/13/2005">Renamed debugger Variables to Values</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/13/2005">Fixed exception being handled twice.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/12/2005">Added VariableCollection.UpdateTo</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/12/2005">Improved code completion for extension methods (currently only enabled for Boo).</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="11/12/2005">SD-538: vb.net specific text editor options not ported to corsavy</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/12/2005">Add code completion for the "override" keyword.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/12/2005">Added public property Debugger to debugger objects. 'debugger' parameter of many constructors inferred from other parameters.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/12/2005">VariableCollection made mutable</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/12/2005">Fixed BOO-536: Forms Designer generated code has bad indentation.
Fixed MemberLookupHelper.GetCommonType.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/12/2005">Don't save the text "whole solution" as directory name, save the correct DocumentIteratorType when searching in a directory.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/12/2005">Fixed SD2-521: Clicking CS1691 error in error list shows error message</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/12/2005">Fixed SD2-557: .resx file becomes invalid when all resources are removed</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/12/2005">The boo CodeDomVisitor now supports local variables (needed for resource manager).
Fixed SD2-523: Opening a new solution should close previously opened files</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/12/2005">PropertyVariable updated to new eval design. Variables can have 'magic' values and have OnValueChanged event.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/12/2005">Redesigned debugger evaluation interface</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/12/2005">Fixed SD2-480 - Forms designer supports localisation.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/12/2005">Fixed two bugs in the C# to VB converter.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/12/2005">Fixed NullReferenceException when typing an OptionStatement.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/11/2005">Added methods for "Set current statement" to IDebugger</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/11/2005">Add "Set current statement" command to text editor context menu.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/11/2005">Use List&lt;SwitchSection&gt; and List&lt;CatchClause&gt; instead of ArrayLists.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/11/2005">Fixed SD2-484 - Designer verbs now displayed in forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/11/2005">Improved keyboard handling in form designer, typing text in the menu designer now works.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/11/2005">Fixed SD2-544: Tooltip stays visible when user starts typing</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/11/2005">Form designer now uses default font for smart tag menus.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/11/2005">Enabled Forms Designer Smart Tags.  Designer Verbs menu item set to be of type Builder in the .addin file</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/11/2005">Fixed some C# output visitor bugs.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/11/2005">Fixed small problem introduced in rev. 714.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/11/2005">Run Autostart before InitializeWorkbench.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/11/2005">Fixed SD2-543: NullReference Exception thrown when viewing VB project properties</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/11/2005">Fixed SD2-552: Class Browser not Refreshing</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/11/2005">Fixed SD2-547: Incorrect text line selected after scrolling text editor window</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/11/2005">Fixed SD2-554: Enum members in output visitor</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/11/2005">Use ParseUtil.ParseX&lt;T&gt;(string) instead of ParseUtil.ParseX(string, Type) for the NRefactory unit tests.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="11/10/2005">SD2-534: Quick XML Doc menu option does nothing; added vb.net support</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/10/2005">When using Ctrl+C or Ctrl+X when nothing is selected, the current line is copied/cut (patch by Martin Nordholts).
Fixed exception when typing a pipe '|' in the new project dialog.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/09/2005">Fixed SD2-507.  Adding a column to a DataGridView was causing a NullReference exception.  Fixed by adding a new TypeDiscoveryService returning types from System.Windows.Forms.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/09/2005">Fixed some small bugs.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/09/2005">Always show tooltips below the code line - patch by Yannick Kiekens (purplebox).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/09/2005">Applied ProjectNodeBuilder patch from Scott Ferret.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/08/2005">Fixed SD2-542.  'Show tooltip when moving mouse over expression' check box set to the value of the CodeCompletionOptions.TooltipsEnabled flag.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/08/2005">Improved C# to Boo converter.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/08/2005">SD2-456.  Focus is now no longer being set back to the form designer after the property pad is clicked.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="11/07/2005">patch from Luc Morin: support for overriding virtual base class properties with the alt-ins mechanism</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/06/2005">Renamed namespace DebuggerInterop to Debugger.Interop</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/06/2005">Renamed namespace DebuggerLibrary to Debugger</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/06/2005">Deleted DebuggerInterop directory. Added Wrappers directory.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/06/2005">Code from DebuggerInterop moved to Interop</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/06/2005">Added headers to debugger interop</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/06/2005">Warning 108 suppressed in the release build of debugger</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/06/2005">Applied form designer patch by Christian Hornung. Fixes SD2-522 and SD2-516.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/06/2005">FileTypeRegisterer now uses HKCU\Software\Classes when there is no write access to HKEY_CLASSES.
SearchAndReplace panel now uses translation database.
Removed many unused resource strings.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/05/2005">Fixed SD2-504: Explicit implementations of generic interfaces cause parser error</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/05/2005">Fixed possible StackOverflowException in BooBinding.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/05/2005">Form designer creates and uses .resx files for new forms and user controls.  Forms that have already been created and are using a .resources file will continue to do so.  Resx files are added to the MSBuild project with the DependentUpon element set to point to its form.  Deleting the form will also delete its Resx file.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/05/2005">Add support for partial classes to the form designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/05/2005">Use shadows, improved colors for debugger tooltip.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/04/2005">Debugger grid child windows now use a custom border instead of SizableToolWindow.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/04/2005">Add AllowLabelEdit to DynamicListItem. Improve drawing of '+' sign.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/04/2005">Fixed debugger tooltip grid.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/04/2005">Exceptions handled properly in .NET 1.1</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/04/2005">Improve Clean task.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/04/2005">Fixed SD2-509: Form Designer duplicates first line of code</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/04/2005">Fixed SD2-520: Changes to Treat Warnings as Errors option ignored</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/03/2005">Fix BooBinding solution file, minor C#-&gt;Boo conversion fix.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/03/2005">Improved measuring of TreeGrid item width.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="11/03/2005">removed that little String hack from SearchPad.cs</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/02/2005">Fixed SD2-471: Sorting of arrays in locals window is wrong</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/02/2005">Function.GetSegmentForOffet is a bit more forgiving</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/02/2005">Removed LoggingService.Debug calls from CompilerMessageView.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/02/2005">Fixed SD2-482: First command line argument not passed to debuggee; 
Debugee version reported in log</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/02/2005">Fixed Thread.Callstack yielding null.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="11/02/2005">Fixed duplicate items in output pad due to race condition in CompilerMessageView.  Addins that use the output pad changed to bring pad to front before adding messages to it.  Added NAnt build file filter when opening files.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/02/2005">Debugger tooltips are filled with real content.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/02/2005">Fixed SD2-512: Form Designer cannot load "Color.FromArgb" definitions</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/02/2005">Fixed SD2-505: Debugger freezes on StackOverflowException</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/02/2005">Fixed obsolete warnings in debugger</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="11/02/2005">.NET 1.1 applications can be debugged</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="11/01/2005">Add code completion support for extension methods in Boo.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="10/31/2005">StateControl refactored. Added WaitForPause()</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="10/31/2005">Help 2.0: added a new checkbox to limit the search results for the current project language if a project is loaded; if not, the checkbox disappears. I was too lazy to build a new version of the translation database, but the strings are entered.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/31/2005">Fixed UTF8 auto-detection. (Thanks to Christian Hornung)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/30/2005">Fixed SD2-510: Deleting a file with local modifications</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="10/30/2005">Thanks to Daniel. I forgot my other *Strip* thing, the ContextMenuStrip in TocPad.cs. The RendererChanged event works for it now.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="10/30/2005">Dynamic Help toolstrip now reacts to the RendererChanged event</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="10/30/2005">Dynamic Help Toolstrip: ProfessionalColorTable used to color the toolstrip</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="10/30/2005">changed the Avalon templates to its real name: WPF (Windows Presentation Foundation)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/30/2005">RegExSearchStrategy now supports replacing "$1" with the group value.
Fixed exception when using invalid RegEx.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/29/2005">Reference libraries from Booc.rsp automatically.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/29/2005">Fixed ObjectDisposedException generated when running XSL transform after splitting the XSLT Output window.  The TextAreaControl/TextArea classes were not removing document event handlers when disposed.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/28/2005">Move some strings into the resource database.
Boo projects import Boo.Lang by default.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/28/2005">ResolvedType on contructor calls now includes type arguments.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/28/2005">Reference Boo.Lang.Useful by default. Automatically copy Boo.Lang.dll to the output directory.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/28/2005">Improved code completion for Boo.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/28/2005">Modify setup to check for .NET 2.0.50727.42 instead of Beta 2.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/28/2005">Fixed a minor bugs in C# to VB and Boo conversion, fixed possible endless loop in VB lexer and a NullReferenceException when using "Go to" in XML files.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/28/2005">Remove the dependency check in release builds for faster starting.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/28/2005">Some changes to resources / font loading.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/28/2005">SharpDevelop now passes properties so that MSBuild accepts them for both the scanning and building steps -&gt; compiling Boo and ILAsm applications and specifying the target Framework version in C# works again.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/28/2005">Replace PostBuildEvent with MsBuild targets.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/27/2005">SharpDevelop should now work on .NET 2.0 final. Implemented a workaround for SD2-485 (Compile solution not working with .NET 2.0 RC1).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/27/2005">Display TreeGrid in debug mode (currently without content).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/27/2005">Add TreeGrid control.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="10/27/2005">changed DefaultFileNodeCommands.cs to accept XAML files; added some XAML file templates (Window, Page, FlowDocument, PageFunction, ResourceDictionary, UserControl)</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="10/27/2005">support for DependentUpon and SubType attributes in XPT project templates added (see the Avalon* templates for a working demo)</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="10/27/2005">Avalon Navigation App template renamed</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="10/26/2005">Avalon page template updated</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="10/26/2005">simple Avalon application template uploaded (for testing only!)</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="10/26/2005">new ApplicationDefinition/Page compiler option; support for external Import commands in XPT project files</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="10/26/2005">updated XML editor for XAML style and schema (does NOT include the Avalon/XAML schema itself)</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/25/2005">Schema errors in task list now use the schema filename.  Fixed problem where each XmlView was creating its own output window category.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/25/2005">Fixed schema errors caught by .NET 2.0 and removed old NAnt 0.84 schema.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/25/2005">Removing SharpAssembly.  The AssemblyScout should be using code completion data from the ProjectContentRegistry and not SharpAssembly.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/25/2005">Most of assembly scout working.  Needs resources from Fidalgo, info view browsing via hyperlinks is disabled, and speed improvements required.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/25/2005">Ported SharpAssembly from Fidalgo.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/25/2005">Can now assign an XSLT stylesheet to an XML file and run transforms.  New XML menu to make it easier to locate xml editor menu items.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/25/2005">Fixed bug in NRefactoryToBooConverter: NullReferenceException when first section in switch-statement was the default section.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="10/25/2005">fixed problem with disposed window</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="10/25/2005">Texteditor now uses DeclarationViewWindow instead of ToolTip (part of SD2-498)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/25/2005">Use a copy of the text/color in the SearchResultPad instead of accessing the real document in the OnPaint method. This fixes some bugs when switching to the SearchResultPad after modifying the document.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/25/2005">Update default layouts.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/25/2005">Fixed SD2-465: Linked files are not imported</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/25/2005">Fixed SD2-497: Allow adding existing files as links.
Boo.Microsoft.Build.Tasks now can embed .resource files.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/24/2005">Fixed SD2-503: WindowActive condition fails</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/24/2005">Add InterpreterWrapper.boo.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/24/2005">Fixed BOO-542: CodeCompletion on interfaces doesn't list inherited Object members.
Fixed crash when cursor was at end of document and the DefinitionViewPad was opened.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/24/2005">Add Boo.InterpreterAddIn.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/24/2005">Fixed possible StackOverflowException in BooBinding. CodeGenerator can now created "Changed"-events and OnEvent-methods.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/23/2005">Allow generating interface implementations using the new CodeGenerator.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/23/2005">Fixed BOO-539: Forms designer does not hook up events to event handlers.
and BOO-538: Syntax colorization of doc-strings with slashes goes awry</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/22/2005">Fixed possible endless loop in Boo ExpressionFinder.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/22/2005">Added FormattingStrategy for Boo and fixed BOO-535: Code completion for generator syntax.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/22/2005">Improved BooBinding:
Allow for code completion on ArrayReturnType and ConstructedReturnType even if they are encapsulated by an InferredReturnType.
Fixed code completion on arrays created through array literals or the "array" builtin.
Recognize variables created by "for" statements if their type is inferred from the element type of the enumerable object.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/22/2005">Fixed BOO-300: #region folding</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/22/2005">Fixed BOO-516: Tooltips don't work in last line of the document</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/22/2005">The commands "Create getter" and "Create property" now generate code using NRefactory. (part of SD2-436)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/21/2005">Fixed bugs in boo code completion.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/21/2005">Fixed problems with RegexpTk.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/21/2005">Fixed SD2-502: Find/Replace dialog toolbar doesn't respect visual style option</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/21/2005">- allow code completion bindings to handle ReturnEditAction by handling '\n'.
- add dummy token "?" to VB lexer.
- use IntegerLiteralResolveResult that doesn't do code completion instead of returning no ResolveResult at all when resolving an integer literal.
- Implemented SD2-501: type inference when typing for both C# and VB.NET.
You can now type "? name = expr;" or "Dim name as ? = expr" and SharpDevelop will fill in the type for you.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/21/2005">Fixed SD2-496: TODO task entries removed after building solution.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/21/2005">Changes in the highlighting are shown when closing the options box, no need to restart SharpDevelop anymore.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/21/2005">Fixed BOO-524 (Autocompletion on import doesn't list only namespaces) in Boo and VB: now only classes that contain public static members are shown in the "import" completion.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/20/2005">Add quotation marks around the post-build event batch file to fix compiling in paths containing a space.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/19/2005">Update conditions in the AddIn schema.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/19/2005">Improved lazy-loading: fixed loading of BackendBindings when text editor was opened.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/19/2005">BuildAddinDocumentation now updates the AddIn schema.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/18/2005">NAnt addin now included in main SharpDevelop solution.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/18/2005">NAnt addin now using SolutionOpen condition.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/17/2005">The Mono build task attempts to locate the Mono install path by reading the registry before falling back to its original method of assuming that the Mcs/Gmcs compilers have been added to the Path.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/17/2005">Fixed C# ExpressionFinder bug when typing "\." inside a string literal.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/17/2005">Add documentation for conditions, rename CombineOpen to SolutionOpen.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/17/2005">Add list with documentation about the doozers.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/17/2005">Fixed SD2-477: Solution import error.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/17/2005">Fixed SD2-492: VS.NET solution converter ignores HintPath attribute for references.
Fixed SD2-491: Solution converter doesn't convert references correctly.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/17/2005">Fixed SD2-488: Highlighting editor does not work for addin-defined syntax modes.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/17/2005">Add attribute completion to BooBinding. 
BOO-436, Smarter Boo integration (Macros, Attributes, Modules, and Imported Classes)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/16/2005">Fixed BOO-347 (BooBinding does not detect methods generated by AST Attributes)
Fixed bug when switching layout configurations.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/16/2005">Fixed BOO-380 (Namespace aliases handled incorrectly during code completion).
Fixed BOO-515 (Expression resolver thinks " is String.Empty).
Fixed BOO-346 (Addin does not reference Boo.Lang.Useful by default)

ParserFoldingStrategy now uses both the RecentCompilationUnit and ValidCompilationUnit for folding. This makes folding more stable in VB and Boo.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/16/2005">Add boo file templates and icons.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/16/2005">Added form designer to BooBinding (BOO-513).
Fixed BOO-511 (#develop should not display boo's "generated" module classes).</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/16/2005">SD2-490.  Fixed problem where the pad contents were not displayed when the default layout was used.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/16/2005">Fixed SD2-483: TreeNode declarations are missing</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/16/2005">Add missing file headers.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/15/2005">BooBinding: Implemented inferring the return type from the "return" statement.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/15/2005">Use Boo.Microsoft.Build.Tasks.dll from repository instead of recompiling it every time in the PostBuildEvent.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/15/2005">Added compilation support to BooBinding.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/15/2005">Added a missing NAnt addin resource string.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/15/2005">Added missing resource strings, removed resource strings from AssemblyAnalyzer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/15/2005">Added NAnt addin from SharpDevelop 1.1/Fidalgo.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/15/2005">Update component library, tried to fix exception when switching back from the form designer when deleting controls from the form so that the caret position is after the end of the document.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/15/2005">Delete old ProjectImporterExporter addin.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/15/2005">The xml folding parser was not setting the filename in the compilation unit causing the Class Browser to throw an unhandled null reference exception.</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="10/14/2005">Minor changes to info document</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/12/2005">Added support for Mono 1.1.9.2</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/12/2005">Added extra MSBuild file extensions to be supported by the XmlFoldingParser.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/12/2005">Added more MSBuild file extensions so they are syntax highlighted.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="10/12/2005">SD2-417 Icon for defintionview pad</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/12/2005">Fixed return type of generic parameters like "ref T[]" and generic references in base types (e.g. IList&lt;T&gt; derives from ICollection&lt;T&gt;).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/12/2005">Fixed SD2-479.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/12/2005">The start command line arguments and the working directory are parsed by the StringParser before the program is run.  This enables the use of custom string tags such as TargetPath, TargetDir, etc.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/12/2005">Included fix for OverrideMethodsCodeGenerator by Yannick Kiekens (purplebox).</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="10/12/2005">SD2-453: ported CustomLineManager from Fidalgo</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="10/11/2005">fixed SD2-445 C# parser fails on default value expression in variable initializer</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/11/2005">Fixed interface code generator for user defined interfaces.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="10/11/2005">ported patch from fidalgo rev 2097</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/11/2005">Don't ignore errors in ReflectionLoader, show real exception instead of failing later with a ArgumentNullException.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="10/10/2005">Patch from Shinsaku Nakagawa. Fixes two IME problems:

1. The font of IME is not changed when option changed.
   (Option-&gt;TextEditor-&gt;General-&gt;Font)
2. The location of IME is not occasionally correct.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/10/2005">Added extra filename extensions to be supported by the XmlFoldingParser.  Folds were only being updated for files with an .xml extension.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/09/2005">Add "Convert buffer to Boo" command to BooBinding.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/09/2005">Deleted some of the unused translation strings.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/09/2005">Fixed SD2-458: Tab is always replaced with 4 spaces</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/08/2005">Added support for commenting/uncommenting a selection of xml.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/08/2005">Fixed SD2-474: Allow targeting other .NET Framework versions.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/08/2005">Fixed SD2-476.  Goto definition now works for unit tests in a test fixture containing a SetUp method.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/08/2005">GotoDefinition executed when double clicking an MbUnitPad test tree node.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/07/2005">Fixed SD2-472 (Cursor disappears off screen whilst pressing right arrow key) and a newly introduce performance problems with large files (&gt;5000 lines).
Added constructor insight support to BooBinding.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/07/2005">Added support for local variables and simple type inference to BooBinding.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/07/2005">Fixed assertion when typing a "RaiseEvent" statement (http://community.sharpdevelop.net/forums/1156/ShowPost.aspx)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/07/2005">Boo implicitly references System.dll and Boo.Lang.dll.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/07/2005">Fixed paths in BooBinding project files.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/07/2005">Add BooBinding.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="10/07/2005">Fixed SD2-473.  A KeyNotFound exception is no longer thrown if the highlighting strategy does not contain a LineComment property.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/05/2005">Improved handling of proportional fonts.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/04/2005">Run MsBuild in a separate thread =&gt; you can continue coding while your code is compiling.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/04/2005">Caret is now displayed at the correct position when using non-monospaced fonts. (but selecting with the mouse still doesn't work)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/03/2005">Use use static readonly collection instance for empty attribute, type parameter and parameter collections.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/03/2005">Fixed SD2-470: When there is a using statement for the current namespace, classes are shown twice in Ctrl+Space</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="10/03/2005">Help 2.0: fixed a bug when selecting the previous or next topic button (browser) with a hidden TOC control; there was an exception because, of course, there was no selection in the TOC control. Now I use the Get*FromUrl method with the current browser URL. btw: some other things changed</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/02/2005">Fixed SD2-420: Non-generic classes and generic classes with the same name collide in the DOM.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/02/2005">Fixed SD2-460: Parse error (inner classes in generic types)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/01/2005">Fixed code completion bug regarding events. Fixed "run unit test in debugger".</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="10/01/2005">Pad layout: included some references for the dynamic help pad to solve issue #2 (http://community.sharpdevelop.net/forums/820/ShowPost.aspx)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/01/2005">Allow references to unbound types in typeof/GetType expressions.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="10/01/2005">Improved performance of "Replace all".</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/30/2005">Fixed NRefactory bugs: VB partial class declarations and attributes with "Global." or "global::" caused parser errors.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/30/2005">Fixed loading of project files created by Visual Studio 2005.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/30/2005">Fixed SD2-440: Icon for local variables and parameters</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/30/2005">Introduced DomCache (a kind of code completion database that is generated on-the-fly for each assembly).
Advantages:
- faster than reflection
- referenced libraries do not need to be looked up during code completion (only when generating the cache)
-&gt; fixes SD2-444 ReflectionOnlyAssemblyResolve is not used when an assembly is only needed inside inner classes
--&gt; Code completion for VB's My-namespace works again
- Assemblies do not need to be hold in RAM (they are now loaded in a separate AppDomain)
-&gt; no more locking problems
-&gt; less memory consumption
Disadvantages:
- higher memory-consumption because currently the file is loaded at once (previously the data was lazy-loaded using Reflection)
-&gt; but there are some optimizations possible (reusing string and DefaultParameter instances) and lazy-loading could be reimplemented similar to what Fidalgo does with its CCDB.
</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/29/2005">dynamic help: needed to fix the Win32 resource... Hm...</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/29/2005">dynamic help: HTML and PNG images included as Win32 resource</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/28/2005">Fixed problem in setup script: wrong install directory was suggested when SharpDevelop 1.x was installed.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/28/2005">Handle exceptions in ICSharpCode.Svn.HistoryViewPanel.GetLogMessages</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/27/2005">Fixed reading project files that start with whitespace.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/27/2005">Fixed SD2-457: C# lexer crash on "0x"</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/27/2005">Switched to NUnit for the NRefactory tests because Mike failed to tell me why he switched to MbUnit and broke ~20 Tests.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/27/2005">Fixed SD2-461: Cannot build projects with umlauts</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/27/2005">The "Load solution" and "New solution" buttons on the start page now work even when JavaScript is disabled in Internet Explorer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/27/2005">Fixed exception when importing VS.NET project without ".user" file.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="09/26/2005">Fixed bug that prevented recompiling due to files locked by the debugger</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="09/26/2005">MbUnit Pad additions - Goto definition implemented, error list displayed after a test run with errors, and after a build the test tree auto-refreshes.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/25/2005">Help 2.0: solution structure changed (you can enable the Dynamic Help by copying the new Addin file)</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/25/2005">dynamic help: some improvements, works with expressions now (ignores documents with more than 1 DevLang attribute)</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/25/2005">Help 2.0: context.html updated</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/24/2005">Fixed SD2-425: Improve project options</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/24/2005">Put ProjectImports into the translation database.
Enabled AutoComplete for the ProjectImports combo box.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/24/2005">Worked on SD2-425 (Improve project options): you can now choose in which section the OutputPath property is stored.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="09/24/2005">added list of project namespaces</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="09/24/2005">added vb.net projectlevel-imports option panel</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/24/2005">Allow user to choose configuration and platform in the project options. (part of SD2-425)</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/24/2005">Help 2.0: some little fixes</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/24/2005">Fixed some P/Invoke declarations where FxCop complained they weren't portable to 64bit and some other complaints from FxCop.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/23/2005">Applied Fidalgo rev. 2075</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="09/21/2005">Added 'Stop tests' toolbar button and context menus to the MbUnit pad.  Go to definition context menu command is not currently working.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/21/2005">Fixed crash when using the "DefaultDebugger" instead of the debugger addin.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/21/2005">Fixed SD-371: Adding empty combine to a combine causes exception
and worked on SD2-425.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/18/2005">dynamic help: fixed a little problem with the 'helpResults' bool</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/17/2005">Fixed SD2-451: Exception thrown when adding new event handler.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/17/2005">Improved project options (more strings translatable, reference paths tab works now)</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/17/2005">dynamic help: fixed a problem with the Project language</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/16/2005">Use InvariantCulture for string comparisons - fixes problems with Turkish locale settings.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/16/2005">dynamic help: uses default entries (s. revision 489), uses the Project language to limit the help results</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/16/2005">dynamic help: created new XML file with default entries (if you want to use it, copy it into the Addin folder)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/15/2005">Put more strings into the translation database.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/14/2005">Application and Signing project options panels now use the translation database.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/14/2005">tried to fix a Virtual PC (no SDK) crash; HiliteMatches restored for testing (it doesn't work here :o( )</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/13/2005">disable 'highlight matching topics' because it doesn't work with the WebBrowser control</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="09/12/2005">File was not being identified as a 'code behind file' if it existed in a subfolder.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/12/2005">Ignore .svn folders when creating setup.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/12/2005">Add prepareRelease.bat (creates ChangeLog.xml and REVISION file)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/12/2005">Fixed InterfaceImplementorCodeGenerator bug (override keyword).</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="09/12/2005">SD2-438.  Form designer now creating, loading and saving resources.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="09/12/2005">Fixed SD2-402:Toolbar in bookmark pad.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/12/2005">some changes/fixes, LoggingService used</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/11/2005">Allow addins to have their project/file templates stored in the addin directory.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/11/2005">dynamic help: new method/type detection (by Robert_G, Delphi-PRAXiS) used for Forms designer support</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/11/2005">Allow find references and rename for local variables and parameters.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/11/2005">Fixed find references on private members in partial classes.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/11/2005">dynamic help: sorting implemented, some other fixed</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/10/2005">Renamed InvocationExpression.Parameters to InvocationExpression.Arguments.
Fixed bug that caused SharpDevelop to add byte order marks to plain ASCII files when UTF-8 was chosen as default encoding.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/10/2005">When renaming a field, ask the user if he also wants to the rename the property.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/10/2005">dynamic help: some changes and fixes and (I hope) improvements</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/10/2005">dynamic help: Forms designer support added; some more improvements</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/10/2005">PropertyPad: SelectedGridItemChanged event for Dynamic Help added</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/09/2005">Reduced number of allocations:
- do not load xml documentation keys into memory but load only the hash code and keep everything else cached on disk.
- made Dom's region a value-type.
- do not create a SortedList&lt;string, IReturnType&gt; for every using statement but only when the using statements actually uses aliases.
Overall SD should use ca. 10 MB RAM less when working on a big solution like SharpDevelop.sln.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/09/2005">dynamic help: debug info enabled; using other ResolveResult types to get more info</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="09/09/2005">Fixed SD2-419:C# Parser bug (methodBase is ConstructorInfo ? #ctor : methodBase.Name).</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="09/09/2005">SharpRefactory tests are now running under MbUnit.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/08/2005">Fixed SD2-439: VB.Net event handlers are lost.
Save layout configuration before switching layout by starting debugger or pressing Shift+Escape.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/08/2005">Show error message when going to designer mode in a file with syntax errors instead of displaying an empty form.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="09/08/2005">SD2-437.  Source code now generated in InitializeComponent method for non-visual components.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/08/2005">dynamic help: some scripting improvements</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/08/2005">I changed some of the CSharp namespace names; there are no bug fixes in this upload</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/04/2005">Fixed some bugs.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/02/2005">dynamic help: I forgot the 3 images for the toolstrip (required to compile) and the HTML file and the 2 *Book.png images for the dynamic help (required to use DH)</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/01/2005">dynamic help: added support for Help 2.0 namespace reloading</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="09/01/2005">dynamic help changed and ready to use</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/28/2005">Implemented hiding of status strip in fullscreen.
Hiding of main menu refactored.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/28/2005">Improved overload resolution by implementing 14.4.2.2 Better function member.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/28/2005">Implemented hiding of main menu and toolbar in fullscreen</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/28/2005">Unavailable variables in debugger handled gracefully</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/27/2005">Fixed bug that was caused by breakpoints set on non-executable lines</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/27/2005">Fixed bug that was caused by static variables maked as ThreadStatic</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/27/2005">Implement type argument inference for generic method calls.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/27/2005">Fixed "copy/cut/paste" in context menus.
Fixed ExpressionFinder bug with identifiers containing underscores.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/27/2005">Improved RefactoringMenuBuilder.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/26/2005">Fixed bug that prevented stepping through anonymous methods.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/26/2005">Fixed bug in search pad when document was changed after the search.
Fixed crash when two classes with the same name were removed from a project content.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/26/2005">Improved overload lookup (but the rules from § 14.4.2.2 are still missing).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/26/2005">Add option to choose between "professional" menu style and system menu style.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/26/2005">Allow AddIns to add their own string resources to the ResourceService.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/26/2005">Fixed bug in InterfaceImplementorCodeGenerator.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/25/2005">Removed IIndexer from ICSharpCode.Dom (replaced by IProperty.IsIndexer)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/25/2005">Fixed some NRefactory bugs (Generic method invocations in VB.NET and output visitor bugs)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/25/2005">Remove quotes from svn:keywords property.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/24/2005">Added fullscreen options panel (no features implemented yet)</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/24/2005">Fixed properties on newly added xml editor test files - removed quotes from the Revision keyword.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/24/2005">Added xml editor tests from Fidalgo branch.  The XmlSchemaCompletionData class is now using the XmlSchemaAttribute's AttributeSchemaType property instead of the obsolete AttributeType which was causing a few of the attribute value tests to fail.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/24/2005">Fixed bug that prevented VB.Net windows forms applications from compiling.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/24/2005">Right click on class and member names (and method invocations) in the text editor now shows the "go to definition" command and the class browser context menu of that item.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/24/2005">Core bugfixes:
 - Fixed exceptions when doozer/condition evaluator is not found.
 - Context menus can now use sub menu builders
Context menu in text editor now shows items from the class member bookmarks.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/24/2005">Fixed assembly loading bug introduced in rev. 429.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/24/2005">Add a "DoEvents" call to the workaround for SD2-426.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/24/2005">Fixed SD2-434: Reference locking issue</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/24/2005">Fixed SD2-433: Deleting references mixes up context menu</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/24/2005">Fixed SD2-432: Project references added to the wrong project.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/24/2005">Add unit tests for CSharpOutputVisitor.
Tried to fix ExternalException when accessing the clipboard.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/24/2005">Fixed bug in C# expression finder that caused CC to fail for "int a = 0; ((NewType)expr).MethodCall(a);".</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/23/2005">Fixed SD2-429: Cannot step into method when property passed as a parameter.
(implemented JMC - just my code)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/23/2005">Added CSharpBinding.Tests project.
Add "run in debugger" command to member bookmarks.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/23/2005">Designer generator now parses the form's code every time a component is added. This ensures that the InitializeComponent's position is correct when adding a new component.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/23/2005">Applied CSharpOutputVisitor patch from Rodrigo B. de Oliveira.
Make go to work with partial classes.
Show expression in tooltips while pressing Ctrl.
Project templates can now specify the BuildAction and CopyToOutputDirectory properties for files.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/23/2005">Removed GC.WaitForPendingFinalizers() because Matt Ward reported it is causing deadlocks.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/23/2005">Fixed SD2-431: Debugger fails on FileLoadException</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/23/2005">Fixed bug: ParseExpression could not parse "a &gt;&gt;= b"</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/23/2005">New files get now a build action dependent on their file extension.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/22/2005">Fixed bug that caused the ParserService to "forget" parsing the projects when a solution was opened with a command line argument.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/22/2005">Fixed SD2-428: Form designer does not load child controls in panels</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/22/2005">Fixed SD2-382: Setting a Breakpoint on an empty line</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/22/2005">Compiler generated functions (like default constructor) are handled like external functions.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/22/2005">SearchResultPad now displays correct line number.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/22/2005">Add some documentation about the addin system.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/22/2005">Make the GotoDialog accept expressions like "Function.cs:line 416" (like in stack traces)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/22/2005">Show debugger tooltips for expressions like "reference.FieldName".</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/22/2005">Included bugfixes from Alex.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/22/2005">Threads can be frozen using threads pad context menu</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/22/2005">Debugger trace messages go to console; VariableListItems moved to its directoy</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/21/2005">VariableCollection can handle dot separated variable names</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/21/2005">Argument names and values can be show/hidden using callstack context menu</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/21/2005">External methods can be show/hidden using callstack context menu</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/21/2005">Local Variables pad cleared when debugger stops</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/21/2005">Fixed Base classes in Local Variables pad</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/21/2005">Added support for included schemas, substitution groups and abstract elements.  Tests not ported over from Fidalgo yet.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/20/2005">Improve project options panels and prepare editing different configurations.
Fixed bug when closing form designer while the property pad was active.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/20/2005">Added first debugger test</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/20/2005">Fixed SD2-414: Breakpoints "invisibly" moving when deleting lines
(implemented DebuggerService.BreakpointChanged event)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/19/2005">Fixed SD2-412: Set as startup project is not implemented.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/19/2005">Use start action for starting projects and give friendly error message when trying to start a class library.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/18/2005">Fixed SD2-404: C#: ExpressionFinder bug with CastExpressions</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/18/2005">Add "default(Type)" expression to C# parser.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/18/2005">Fixed SD2-423: Cast to array types cause parser error.
Fixed C# lexer bug with long hexadecimal literals.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/18/2005">Added support for accessor modifiers to C# parser (public int Property { get {} protected set {}})</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/18/2005">SD2-421: Add msbuild file template</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/18/2005">Add null coalescing operator to C# lexer and parser.</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="08/18/2005">Added version number to default install directory, the default is now %programfiles%\sharpdevelop\2.0\. Program group is now also SharpDevelop 2.0. Uninstall key is SharpDevelop2, to not clash with 1.0 installation (SxS is now possible with installer)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/18/2005">Fixed SD2-387: Main Menu: Sub menu position wrong</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/18/2005">Fixed SD2-416: Multi-instance Search and Replace dialog</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/18/2005">Improved event handler completion.
Removed SharpZipLib.
Fixed SD2-415 and SD2-418.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/18/2005">Allow writing a space after "+=" completion without closing the completion window.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/17/2005">Add NUnit.Framework again.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/17/2005">Removed NUnit project reference from main SharpDevelop solution.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/17/2005">Main menu and toolbar initialised after all the pads so that keyboard shortcuts work for the various View-Pad menu items without needing the menu to be displayed at least once.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="08/17/2005">Removed nunit and nprof</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="08/17/2005">Changed some little translation issues. Re-Arranged tools menu.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/17/2005">Update English and German StringResources (combine -&gt; solution).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/17/2005">Fixed SD2-410: Goto definition doesn't work for array types</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/17/2005">Fixed SD2-411: Code completition doesn't show parent class (nested classes)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/16/2005">Fixed forms designer to reparse the file when switching to the designer tab.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/16/2005">Show properties (F4) now works in form design mode.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/16/2005">Ported changes from Fidalgo rev 2038, ivokovacka.
Fixed more NRefactory bugs.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="08/16/2005">added very basic event handler code completition (appears after typing '+='); still many things to do here</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/16/2005">Added scrollbars to debugger Exception Dialog</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/16/2005">VB parser: Declarations in the form "Dim a(10) As Integer" were not recognized as array declarations.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/16/2005">Fixed C# parser bug: anonymous methods without parameter list were not supported.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/15/2005">NRefactory bugfixes (C#: For initializers added twice and VB: Custom event regions not stored in AST)</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="08/15/2005">Debugger.Interop assembly removed</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="08/14/2005">changed FullTypeName search to DynamicHelp engine</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/13/2005">Patched docking suite. Take care on docking library updates:
Fixed warnings in docking suite. Tabs can be closed with middle mouse button.
Included bug fixes from docking suite's bug tracker on SF.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/13/2005">Improved C# -&gt; VB converter (For-Statement is converted to ForNextStatement).
Fixed VB parser (CSByte, CUShort, CUInt, CULng cast operators were missing).</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="08/13/2005">enabled an early version of F1 help</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/13/2005">When displaying xml namespaces the autocompletion list now resizes to fit the longest string.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/13/2005">SearchAndReplaceDialog remembers it's location and can be closed with Escape.
Fixed ExpressionFinder when cursor was at the end of the document.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/13/2005">Changed the namespace for the form designer context menu commands.  Added ICSharpCode.SharpDevelop runtime to FormDesigner.addin.  Form designer context menus now working.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/13/2005">Added F1 help to text editor and forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/13/2005">Fixed SD2-385: After project run Source/Abstract Content tabs are missing</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/12/2005">Fixed some bugs.
Add new GotoDialog (replaces GotoLineNumberDialog).
The GotoDialog accepts line numbers, class names and file names. (Examples: "120", "MainClass", "Main.cs, 120")</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/12/2005">Fixed SD2-399: Hide bookmarks inside folded regions</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/12/2005">Fixed SD2-380: TODO Parsing Bug.
OpenTaskView now sorts it's entries, this prevent having the task entries "jump around" if you edit a file containing tasks.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/12/2005">Add context menu to class browser.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/12/2005">Fixed SD2-400: Importing classes (VB.NET).
Fixed code completion on "value" in property setters.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/12/2005">Fixed drag'n'drop of components from the side bar to the form designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/11/2005">AutoHide pads are initalized when they are expanded (not when they are first clicked on).
Fixed CompilerMessageView refresh problem.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/11/2005">Small bugfixes, updated translation, modified SVNChangeLogToXml to use NSvn instead of svn.exe; created publish.bat which automatically builds SharpDevelop, runs SVNChangeLogToXml and then builds the setup.Remove NUnitPad (MbUnit can run NUnit tests).
</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/11/2005">Small bugfixes, updated translation, modified SVNChangeLogToXml to use NSvn instead of svn.exe; created publish.bat which automatically builds SharpDevelop, runs SVNChangeLogToXml and then builds the setup.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/11/2005">Fixed two small code completion bugs:
- code completion does not show members of base class when some interface of the class does not exist
- when referenced assemblies had inter-dependencies (Assembly A depends on B), code completion on properties in A that used a type in B would not work.
ReflectionParameter: Read "ref/out/params" modifier correctly.
ReflectionProjectContent: Use ReflectionLoad also for GAC assemblies specified by partial name.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="08/10/2005">minor fixes (MSDN is the default search page again) and cosmetic (printer picture for ContextMenuStrip in TocPad.cs)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/10/2005">Improved MbUnit addin.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/10/2005">Add MbUnit and MbUnit-addin.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/10/2005">When loading referenced assemblies for code completion that have missing dependencies, try to find best available version.
For example, when using a library compiled against .NET 1.0; but only .NET 2.0 is installed, redirect the ReflectionOnlyAssemblyResolve event to load the .NET 2.0 version of System.dll instead.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/09/2005">Use LoggingService instead of Console.WriteLine.
Fixed a little bug in attribute completion.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/08/2005">Update to log4net 1.2.9.0 and remove some parts of log4net (compiled documentation, NAnt, builds for mono) to reduce download size of repository.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/08/2005">Use .Net SDK help ("MS.NETFramework.v20.en") as default collection displayed in help addin.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/08/2005">Copy GacUtil2 to tools directory.
Small bugfix for code completion and ErrorList.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/08/2005">Cut/Copy/Paste menu+toolbar commands now also work for normal text boxes and combo boxes (e.g. on the project's property pages).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/08/2005">Fixed SD2-397: Empty Project Scout has visually enabled (not grayed out) icons.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/08/2005">Fixed SD2-374: Compiler warnings during debugging.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/08/2005">Fixed SD2-405: Invisible menu item can be run by shortcut.
Fixed SD2-376: Debugger: Menu consistency.
Added caching to SearchClassReturnType (dramatically improves code completion performance in classes that have many base types like XmlView).</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="08/08/2005">Setup message changed</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="08/08/2005">Updated to v2.0 and added a 2.0 blurb to the Intro</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/07/2005">Rename configuration folder from .ICSharpCode\Corsavy to .ICSharpCode\SharpDevelop2</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/07/2005">Remove old help. Deactivate run of help register tool.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/07/2005">Fixed SD2-398: Add support for nullables to the C# parser.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/07/2005">Code completion improvements.
Made forms designer capable of loading classes that don't use fully qualified names for the fields.
Added solution that includes unit tests.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/07/2005">Fixed SD2-401: Using aliases for classes.
Usings like "using StringCollection = System.Collections.Generic.List&lt;string&gt;" are now valid and code completion works correctly for them.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/06/2005">Fixed SD2-403: Find references does not find indexer calls.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/06/2005">Add SharpDevelop help / help register application.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/06/2005">Fixed compile errors.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/06/2005">Update default layouts. Fixed help document highlighting.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/06/2005">Made HtmlHelp2 addin use the normal search results pad.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/06/2005">Move XmlEditor files in Src/Resources subdirectories.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/06/2005">Fixed SD2-293 (Creating any C++ Project fails with a NullReferenceException).
Fixed exception when quickly closing multiple files during the initial parser run.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/06/2005">Improved lazy-loading.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/06/2005">Made UpdateAssemblyInfo use NSvn instead of svn.exe.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/05/2005">Remove some Console.WriteLine() calls; catch some exceptions which previously were ignored silently or just dumped to the console.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/05/2005">Update XmlEditor file headers. Display browser's status text in status bar.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/05/2005">Critical bug fixed (MenuCommands didn't work)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/05/2005">Made Help addin use the default browser view content. (moved advanced toolbar from help addin to Base)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/05/2005">Added HtmlHelp2 addin.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="08/05/2005">File tabstrip context menu now working again. (Patched docking suite. Take care on dockin library updates.)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/04/2005">Included XmlEditor addin.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/04/2005">Added XmlEditor addin.
Fixed some bugs.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/04/2005">Fixed SD2-395: Deleting a file from Project Scout causes NSvn.Core.NotVersionControlled Exception.</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="08/04/2005">Worked on Boyer-Moore search strategy</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/04/2005">Added ILAsmBinding and ICSharpCode.Build.Tasks (library for additional MSBuild tasks like ILAsm)</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="08/04/2005">Worked on forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/03/2005">Added checks for invalid filenames. (SD2-394)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/03/2005">Fixed SD2-384 and SD2-386.</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="08/03/2005">Finished the Lexer position test, please add some more VB test if you know the language better than me :)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/03/2005">Use translation database for code completion options panel and "refactoring bookmark".</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="08/03/2005">worked on VB Positions, added some C# tests</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="08/03/2005">removed one more Console.WriteLine</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="08/03/2005">worked on Positions and removed some debug Console.WriteLine</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="08/03/2005">Worked on VB.NET Forms Designer.'</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/03/2005">Fixed SD2-388 and SD2-389.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/03/2005">Fixed SD2-396: Opening a Visual Studio Solution with #D causes Error "... is not a valid solution file".</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/02/2005">Fixed SD2-379 (Exception dialog box).
Fixed bug with empty catch statements.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="08/02/2005">worked on translation.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="08/02/2005">worked on main menu translation.</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="07/31/2005">tryed to implement a BoyerMoore algorithm, commented out, only copied from a web site</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="07/31/2005">added some LexerPasotionTest for VB too. The Positions after a \n in VB not working in the Moment, kommented test out wich are not working...</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/31/2005">Fixed text editor caret positioning bug. (occured with fonts that had different font withs for bold and plain chars)</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="07/31/2005">refactoring of the lexer is now ready: reader, line and col are now private in the AbstractLexer, the derived classes do not need to handle positioning stuff</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/31/2005">Fixed option update bug.</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="07/31/2005">C# lexer ready, begin with vb lexer.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/31/2005">worked on forms designer loading.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/31/2005">fixed wrong test</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/31/2005">worked on codedom ast codegenerator. codedom code generation is now more in line with the .net codedom formsdesigner output.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/31/2005">inserted operator declartions into DOM. fixed locations of operator declarations, this enabled folding for them</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="07/31/2005">added some Token position tests and refactored the c# Lexer. Want to put all line and col management in the AbstractLexer. BV Lexer needs to be updated to use the new ReaderRead and ReaderPeek functions. line and col should be private and Line and Col readonly.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/31/2005">fixed exception when referenced project that was thrown when a referenced project wasn't part of the open project</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/31/2005">replace and replace all works</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/31/2005">unit tests for vb.net type level declarations</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/30/2005">assign correct document iterator</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/30/2005">taken out test assemblies from main project.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/30/2005">nunit pad now working.</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="07/30/2005">Start to write PositionTest for the Lexer and added the NRefactoryTest Project to the SD combine</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/30/2005">Errorlist labels are now updated.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/30/2005">fixed positions</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/30/2005">correct positions of type members with modifiers</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="07/30/2005">go to definition now works for parameters too</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/30/2005">work on custom events</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/30/2005">Worked on bookmarks</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/30/2005">added operator overload support to vb grammar</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/30/2005">Fixed bug in ActiveContent property in SdiLayout. (Bug affected the functionalty of cut/copy/paste. updated the sidebar control library to .NET 2.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/30/2005">Fixed CodeDOM output bug which prevented the forms desinger from working.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/28/2005">Keyword completion is not activated in comments anymore.
VB lexer now reads documentation comments.
Resolver now distinguishes between Type and Default context -&gt; property declarations like "public Size Size {" resolve properly (TypeResolveResult for the first Size, MixedResolveResult for the second)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/27/2005">Small bug fixes.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/27/2005">Bugfix - Arguments of static functions</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/27/2005">Improved prjx imported.
Added importer for VS.NET [2003] projects.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/26/2005">correct test</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/26/2005">custom events support</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/26/2005">Fixed function switching bug, debugger window acivated if debugee pauses</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/26/2005">Fixed some resolver bugs.
Added "bookmark" for classes.
Added support for finding references to classes and renaming classes.
Renamed the Erbauer/Auswerter classes.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/26/2005">Added some error messages, worked on function and thread switching</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/26/2005">Reworked debugger state control</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/25/2005">Bugfixes - Local variables on thread without symbols; Can't click on function without symbols; Added CurrentFunction to NDebugger</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/25/2005">Ported some fixes for unit test mode from Fidalgo rev. 2014.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/25/2005">Rename Erbauer/Auswerter files.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/25/2005">Bugfixes - Thread and Callstack switching; unmanaged functions refused</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/25/2005">Bugfixes - no CurrentFunction in Threads pad handled, Method signature blob ignored now, dereference fail handled</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/25/2005">Prototype of SetIP</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/25/2005">Rename Erbauer/Auswerter directories.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/25/2005">When typing a variable declaration like "List&lt;string&gt; list = new ***", the new-completion popup preselects "List&lt;string&gt;".</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/25/2005">Exception interception</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/25/2005">Exception dialog uses TextBox and is bit more informative</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/25/2005">Improved support for partial classes.
Improved C# new completion.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/24/2005">Bugfixing, handled exceptions handled faster</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/24/2005">Fixed C# parser (added support for generic methods inside interfaces).
Changed CurrentLineBookmark to be invisible in BookmarkPad and not saved.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/24/2005">CurrentLineBookmark does not use whole line, 'Debug' layout used during debugging</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/24/2005">Fixed parser crash introduced in last revision.
Made debugger addin lazy-loading.
Fixed bug in MarkerStrategy causing parts of removed markers still being rendered.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/24/2005">IsProcessRunningd and IsDebugging replaced with IsCurrentProcessSafeForInspection</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/24/2005">Removed IsProcessRunningChanged and IsDebuggingChanged from NDebugger</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/24/2005">Fixed code completion bugs regarding "global::"/"Global".</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/24/2005">Worked on stepping (sometimes it was necessary to step more times)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/24/2005">Fixed some code completion bugs.
Reactivated FiletypeRegisterer addin.
Added HandleConditions property to IErbauer.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/23/2005">added vb.net completion after several expressions and keywords. added insight for vb.net</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/23/2005">Updating my headers</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/23/2005">Worked on Local variables pad</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/23/2005">.csproj/.vbproj files can now be opened directly (.sln is automatically created)
Files from command line arguments are opened instead of the start page.
Made GetWorkbench() in ParserUpdateThread thread-safe. (fixes NullReferenceException when closing files while the parser thread is running).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/23/2005">Fixed bug in ReflectionOnly assembly loading.
Fixed crash when a pad could not be loaded.
Added publisher policy.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/22/2005">added vb.net keyword completition. todo: add completition for special statements, show insight</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/22/2005" />
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/22/2005">Applied new header to all source files.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/22/2005">Fixed solution saving (the order of the solution folders would reverse every time the solution is saved).
Added tool to set the file headers.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/22/2005">Added generic methods to VB.Net grammar.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/22/2005">Added panel with options for code completion.
Fixed bug in CodeCompletionListView (when entering a name that did not exist in the list, the ListView didn't remove the current selection but selected the first entry).
Made MessageService.ShowError use the ExceptionBox in release builds.
Made ExceptionBox link to the mailing list instead of the bugs forum.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/21/2005">added 'open solution' button to main toolbar (common task)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/21/2005">Code completion remembers frequently used items and prefers them in SelectItemWithStart().</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/21/2005">Added code completion on type parameters in generic classes.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/21/2005">Added tool to put revision number into AssemblyInfo files.
Included revision number in splash screen.
Made ReflectionClass load custom attributes.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/20/2005">Some error checking, Debugger.Interop update</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/20/2005">Added code completion for attributes.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/20/2005">Added support for My.Forms.
Added support for ImportProjectItems.
Reworked NRefactory to use List&lt;AttributeSection&gt; instead of ArrayList for attributes and List&lt;ParameterDeclarationExpression&gt; instead of ArrayList for parameter declarations.
Added Ctrl+'.' debug code completion.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/19/2005">A little modification of the hack</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/19/2005">Really nasty hack to force release of debug symbols</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/19/2005">WindowsDebugger cleaned up</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/19/2005">Worked on breakpoints</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/19/2005">Added support for code completion on partial classes.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/19/2005">Reworked DebuggerService, IDebugger, DefaultDebugger and Debugger menu</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/19/2005">Added code completion for the "My" namespace.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/19/2005">Added generics support to the VB.Net parser.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/19/2005">Removed old code from DebuggerService</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/19/2005">Replacing EventHandler with generics EventHandler</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/19/2005">All events inherit from DebuggerEventArgs</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/19/2005">Fixed some code completion bugs.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/18/2005">Worked on code completion.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/18/2005">CurrentProcess, CurrentThread and CurrentFunction set in ManagedCallback</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/18/2005">System.Diagnostics not used in debugger anymore</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/18/2005">Added code completion after keywords like 'using', 'new', 'as', 'is', ...</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/18/2005">Some custom exceptions removed</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/18/2005">Added Process collection</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/17/2005">Handling of CurrentThread and CurrentFunction changed</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/17/2005">Improved code completion.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/17/2005">Some call forwarders removed</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/17/2005">Created public constructors for SourcecodeSegment, changes in Breakpoint.cs</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/17/2005">Debugger lazy loading bug fixed</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/17/2005">Function.cs refactored to use MetaData wrapper</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/17/2005">Extended MetaData wrapper</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/17/2005">ObjectVariable.cs refactored to use MetaData wrapper</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/17/2005">Started MetaData wrapper</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/16/2005">Debugger lazy loading</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/16/2005">Continue postponed to OnDebuggingPaused()</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/16/2005">Finally found a walkaround for LocalVarPad visual issue</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/16/2005">Small improvements.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/16/2005">Improved C# &lt;-&gt; VB.Net conversion.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/16/2005">Refactoring function.cs</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/16/2005">A bit work on properties</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/16/2005">Parser now inserts documentation into the AST.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/15/2005">ported path from fidalgo revision 2003</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/15/2005">Fixed C# code completion when an expression had two meanings (eg. type and property: 'Size' in classes deriving from Form)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/15/2005">Fixed some C# &lt;-&gt; VB conversion bugs.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/15/2005">Fixed ctrl-space code completion.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/15/2005">C# &lt;-&gt; VB.Net converters now convert comments.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/15/2005">TextEditorControl now auto-detects the file encoding. When saving, the file is saved with the old encoding.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/14/2005">Added MyProxy, preparing NDebugger for MTA</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/13/2005">Playing with Remoting 2</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/12/2005">Playing with Remoting</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/11/2005">Added custom Remoting sinks</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/11/2005">Debugger made less static 2</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/11/2005">Debugger made less static</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="07/11/2005">Removed length limitation on unmanaged strings</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="07/03/2005">improved vb.net indentation (http://icsharpcode.net/OpenSource/SD/Forum/topic.asp?TOPIC_ID=9042)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/25/2005">Fixed code completion problems when one referenced assembly has references to other assemblies.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/25/2005">Worked on SubversionAddIn.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/25/2005">Move SubversionAddIn back (doesn't solve my problem with MSBuild)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/25/2005">Moved SubversionAddin.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/25/2005">Added &lt;Include&gt; erbauer.
Worked on SubversionAddIn.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/24/2005">Worked on SubversionAddIn.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/24/2005">Fixed code completion bugs with inner classes.
Modified SubversionAddIn to compile against Corsavy.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/23/2005">Fixed some issues with code completion and the class browser.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/22/2005">Fixed some ClassBrowser bugs. Included splashscreen from Korona.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/22/2005">Fixed code completion in files containing character literals like '\xFF'.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/22/2005">QuickClassBrowser performance fix.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/11/2005">Fixed some small bugs.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/27/2005">Fixed code completion for generic methods.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/23/2005">Fixed C# ExpressionFinder to support generics.
Implemented field references on generic classes in c# parser ('SomeGenericClass&lt;string&gt;.StaticProperty = "Beispiel";')
Fixed form designer code generic (use "this" instead of class name).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/22/2005">Added invocation of generic methods to c# parser.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/21/2005">Added anonymous methods to c# parser.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/21/2005">Fixed code completion bugs regarding generic methods.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/21/2005">Fixed generic class and method declarations in C# parser.</Change>
  <Change author="Mathias Simmack" date="05/20/2005">'FormDesigner.addin'patches to access the Customize dialog (I needed some of the new .NET 2.0 controls; these *Strip* things :o))</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/19/2005">Renamed FileUtility.IsEqualFile to FileUtility.IsEqualFileName (this was a successful test of 'rename').</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/19/2005">Implemented "rename" refactoring.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/19/2005">Implemented "Find references".</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/18/2005">Added "find overrides".</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/17/2005">Added constructor overload lookup.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/17/2005">IconMargin now shows icons for methods and properties that can be clicked to execute actions on the properties/methods.
Currently, only "go to base class" is available for overridden methods, which jumps to the method that was overridden.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/16/2005">Bookmarks (and breakpoints) are saved in the project preferences.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/16/2005" />
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/16/2005">Breakpoints are now a special kind of bookmarks.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/11/2005">Added xml documentation cache. Xml documentation files with more than 300 entries are now converted into a binary format that does not require to be hold in memory to look up the documentation.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/11/2005">Even more performance improvements for the LoadSolutionProjectsThread. Fixed SkipCurrentBlock() in C# lexer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/10/2005">Improved performance of parser run after opening a solution (really big improvement!!).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/09/2005">Fixed VB code completion. Fixed method overload lookup.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/09/2005">Resolver is now using ExtractMethod to parse only the current method to get local variables.
This removes the need to save the NRefactory-CompilationUnit in the Tag property of the AST-CompilationUnit.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/09/2005">Fixed assertion when parsing method declaration with an unnamed parameter (when the user is still typing): use name '?' instead.
Double-Clicking on the definition view pad now jumps to the location clicked on in the main view.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/09/2005">Fixed bug in C# parser that could generate null reference as method invocation argument (+added unit tests).
Fixed bug regarding FileSystemWatcher to prevent crash when file was changed externally.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/08/2005">Fixed string splitting.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/08/2005">Implemented ExtendedWebBrowser to get the NewWindow event.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/08/2005">CurrentAmbience now uses the ambience of CurrentProject.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/07/2005">Small bug fixes (StatusBar, ProjectContent).
Also, GetCorLibProjectContent() is now called directly after startup (so the classes are loaded while the user chooses the project)
Fixed output path of some addins in release build.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/07/2005">Display parsing progress in status bar when opening project.
Fixed cross thread calls on SWF controls.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/07/2005">Fixed code completion for VB.NET. Implemented LanguageProperties to control case sensivity for project content.
Fixed solution loading to first create all project contents and then create the references to each other.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/06/2005">Fixed SD-338: Selecting text with the mouse by clicking in the gutter</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/06/2005">More CC bugfixes.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/06/2005">Worked on code completion.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/06/2005">Implemented code completion for generics. Fixed code completion for arrays.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/06/2005">Worked on code completion for generics.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/06/2005">Worked on SharpDevelop.Dom (just a step closer to being able to begin working on generics support :)).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/06/2005">Ctrl-Space completion now shows generic type parameters after class name.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/05/2005">Fixed some bugs in code completion and error drawing.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/05/2005">Optimized StringParser.
Included PieceTableTextBufferStrategy from David McCloskey, but it's currently commented out.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/05/2005">Merged Dom/Implementations/Abstact* and Dom/NRefactoryResolver/*.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/05/2005">Renamed some files Abstract* -&gt; Default*.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/05/2005">Worked on SharpDevelop.Dom (merging Implementations/Abstact* and NRefactoryResolver/*) + some bug fixes when creating new projects.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="05/05/2005">fixed SD-353: Wrong position of insight window when horizontal ruler is visible</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="05/02/2005">added shadows keyword to syntax highglightning definition</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="05/01/2005">Added log4net.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/01/2005">AddInBuildingGuide modified for Corsavy.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="04/30/2005">Minor fixes</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="04/30/2005">Debugger stepping made more stable</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/26/2005">Add SharpDevelopAddin project template.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/24/2005">Replaced LoadWithPartialName through Assembly.Load, it seems to do the same job in .NET 2.0.
Optimized the StringParser a bit.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/24/2005">ParserService does not lock parsed files anymore.
Moved common options panel from C# and VB.NET to base.
Fixed bug in property pad by introducing PropertyContainer (combined set of DesignerHost, SelectableObjects and SelectedObject).
The PropertyPad now automatically shows the PropertyContainer of the active ViewContent.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/23/2005">Fixed some properties in the project files.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/23/2005">Moved debugger pads into their own subcategory in the view menu.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/23/2005">Fixed project template options.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/23/2005">Fixed docking of project options panel.
Definition tooltip does not try to override text marker tooltips anymore.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/22/2005">Add definition view pad.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="04/21/2005">Property evaluation in the debbuger disabled</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/20/2005">Fixed bug that prevented project scout treeview from redrawing when opening folder without contents.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/19/2005">Made tooltip static so only one tooltip can be displayed at one time.
Tooltip now shows current value of local variables/parameters when debugging.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="04/19/2005"> * Caching of Variable.CorType
 * Base classes disabled in Local Variables Pad
 * Icons in subtrees of Local Variables Pad fixed</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="04/19/2005">Icons in Local Variables Pad fixed</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="04/19/2005">ExceptionBox is not used if #D is started under debugger</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="04/18/2005">corDebug.Terminate() crashed the #D on exit</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="04/18/2005">Release build fixed (but nunit.framework still must be in GAC)</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="04/18/2005">"workingDirectory" and "arguments" used in CreateProcess 
(Since 2.0.50215 this prevented the debugger to start)</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="04/18/2005">Debugger Interop updated to Beta 2</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/18/2005">Fixed SD-318 and SD-347. Many small changes.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/13/2005">Improved XmlDoc to text conversion.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/13/2005">Update DockPanelSuite, fixes bug that views were not properly closed.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/13/2005">Included file icons from Wolfgang Bartelme.
Fixed exception when loading project that has a .xml file declared as "compile".</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/28/2005">Language bindings can now determine on what characters and keywords code completion should be triggered.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="03/14/2005">adopted patch from fidalgo revision 1807</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/13/2005">Fixed StackOverflowException when property ReflectionIndexer.Parameters is used.
CC does not pop up on integer literals anymore.
Fixed focus stealing when moving mouse over FoldMargin.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/13/2005">Resolver can now find correct overload in a method invocation.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/10/2005">Fixed some bugs.
PropertyCodeGenerator can work with fields like '_fieldname' or 'm_fieldname'.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/10/2005">MSBuildProject now uses Microsoft.Build.Engine instead of calling MSBuild.exe.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/09/2005">Fixed bugs in ParserUpdateThread.
Fixed bug in InsightDataProviders.
Added unit test for CC lookup of a method with multiple overloads.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="02/28/2005">#D now runs under the latest .NET Framework.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/03/2005">Fixed MessageView bug.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/02/2005">Many bugfixes/improvements in the resolver.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/01/2005">ParserService now supports ProjectReferences.
Go to definition now works for local variables.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/31/2005">Added feature: go to definition (Ctrl-Enter)
Set warninglevel to 4 for Core + Base (somehow it was set to 0 -&gt; a bug in AbstractMember.cs was hidden)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/30/2005">Fixed Lexer bug (both C#/VB): OverflowException was thrown when dot was at end of expression.
Fixed Lexer bug (C#): OverflowException was thrown when integer literal was at end of expression.
Added unit tests for literals.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/30/2005">Reintroduced ICSharpCode.SharpDevelop.Tests, adjusted NRefactoryResolverTests for new Resolver.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/30/2005">Fixed tooltip flickering and a resolver bug.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/30/2005">Fixed some bugs in resolver; tooltip now uses ExpressionFinder and GetXmlDocumentation.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/29/2005">Tooltip now shows the type of variables.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="01/29/2005">Added new ResolveResult that gives information about the expression being resolved.
Currently it is used for code completion and method insight.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="01/28/2005">Introduced new debugger class Process</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="01/28/2005">Moved some code from WindowsDebugger to DebuggerService</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/28/2005">Fixed parser update thread.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/28/2005">Text markers can now specify foreground color.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="01/27/2005">Removed some silent fails. Bugfixing</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="01/27/2005">Worked on exceptions; Added ExceptionHistoryPad</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="01/26/2005">Added exception handling form</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="01/26/2005">Implemented custom marshalling for new debugging API callbacks</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/24/2005">took out some writelines.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="01/23/2005">Worked on replacing strong typed collections with generics ones</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="01/22/2005">Files in Debugger.Core reorganized</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="01/22/2005">DebuggerInterop.Symbols.il replaced by ISymWrapper.dll</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/22/2005">Execute without debugger now works. (#D doesn't currently work in debugging mode).</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/22/2005">updated dockpanel suite.</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="01/22/2005">worked on Resolver (SearchDefinition)</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="01/22/2005">Some unversioned directories marked to be ignored.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="01/21/2005">Worked on evaluation of properties in debugger</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="01/20/2005">Fixed updating of debugger pads</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="01/20/2005">AssemblyInfo.cs moved to Configuration folder</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/20/2005">worked on Resolver</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="01/20/2005">fixed bug in propertygrid</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/20/2005">the compiler message view now uses our text editor.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/20/2005">Changed default layouts. (Because of the debugger panels.)</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/20/2005">Font selection panel is now much faster in initalization.</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="01/19/2005">Initial Debugger Import</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="01/14/2005">removed debugging output</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="01/14/2005">vb.net folding works</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="01/12/2005">%windir% used to get Windows directory in batch files</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/11/2005">VB.NET backend now works.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/11/2005">Worked on code completion layer.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/11/2005">Worked on main menu. Complex conditions now support failed actions</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/11/2005">Worked on IL backend. But I don't know how to plug in a new msbuild 'language'.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/10/2005">Worked on code completion layer.</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="01/10/2005">#d builds again; work on the parser layer</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="01/10/2005">unitised vb.net language name; added vb.net binding to the main solution</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="01/10/2005">added initial vb.net binding (very c#-ish at the moment)</Change>
  <Change author="Markus Palme" date="01/10/2005">removed old vb.net backend binding</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/10/2005">The refactoring of the upper code completion layer has begun ...</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/10/2005">project contents can now reference other project contents (greatly reducing loading times/memory consumption). XmlDocumentation is now loaded &amp; cached (greatly increasing loading times/memory consumption).</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/09/2005">View menu builder works again.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/06/2005">Added Solution file format validation</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/06/2005">taken out the description= tags of the menus (They're unused since a while ...)</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/06/2005">Fixed compilation bug.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/06/2005">Fixed property grid bug (caused by lazy loading)."</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="01/06/2005">fixed bug in topological sort and startet to write tests for it.</Change>
  <Change author="Andrea Paatz" date="01/06/2005">fixed build error: sharpDevelop.ico has an absolute path from Mike. Now the path is relativ and should work for everyone.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/06/2005">Core tests are in the solution.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/06/2005">Moved abstract project.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/06/2005">Exception box is now working again.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/05/2005">Worked on #D</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/05/2005">overworked task subsystem a bit.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/05/2005">Code generator (Alt+ins) now works again. fixed texteditor drawing bug.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/05/2005">Forgot to check in some changes.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/05/2005">Worked on #Develop. Search &amp; Replace panel now has 2 different view modes. ExtTreeView drawing is now more smooth. Fixed some issues.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/05/2005">Removed nunit binaries.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/05/2005">Slightly improved C# formatting. custom edit actions are now working again.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/04/2005">References can now be removed. Rename/remove operations are now faster with really big projects</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/04/2005">addin scout now working again.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/04/2005">Nunit pad is now working again. Switched to NUnit 2.2.2</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/04/2005">Worked on project options.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/04/2005">Improved toolbar refresh.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/04/2005">Path of the errors in files are now parsed correctly.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/04/2005">Fixed little issues.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/04/2005">Fixed many little issues.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/04/2005">Removed winformsUI binaries.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/04/2005">Corrected output path of the filetype registerer (his job should be done by the installer) and resource editor.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/04/2005">Added start project as context menu command for projects.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/04/2005">Fixed bug in text editor options panel.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/04/2005">Corsavy is now self-hosting. Hopefully no more build files are out of sync with project files issues ...</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="01/04/2005">created trunk folder.</Change>
</ChangeLog>