<ChangeLog project="SharpDevelop">
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/15/2009">Fixed compiler warning in Boo AddIn.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/15/2009">Fixed forum-10068: members from COM Interop assembly not shown in code completion.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/15/2009">Fixed forum-10067: incorrect indentation for nested if-statements without braces.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="09/14/2009">fixed SD2-1568 - Using unsupported evaluation features in conditional breakpoints causes an exception</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="09/11/2009">added workaround to fix http://community.sharpdevelop.net/forums/p/10063/27905.aspx</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/10/2009">Revert r4902.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="09/10/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/IOutputAstVisitor.cs: Exposed some properties
  from the abstract output formatter into the interface.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/09/2009">Disable IME when ICSharpCode.TextEditor is used in .NET 4.0.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="09/06/2009">fixed some localization issues in Profiler options panels</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="09/06/2009">Update string resources.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/05/2009">Fixed ArgumentOutOfRangeException in Boo forms designer and added workaround for another possible ArgumentOutOfRangeException (also when leaving the designer).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/05/2009">Fixed IsAccessible for "protected internal" members. (forum-9974)</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="09/05/2009">- updated English translation
- updated German translation
- fixed small bug in QueryView
- fixed localization issues in GeneralOptionsPanel</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/05/2009">Immediately rename form class when a form is renamed in the designer (avoids side-effects in IViewContent.Save).
This fixes forum-9916 (error closing Sharp Development IDE after renaming a form).</Change>
  <Change author="Christian Hornung" date="09/05/2009">Fixed SD2-1588 - Automatic SVN add of forms designer .resx file fails.
The stream which the resource file is saved to is now closed before the SVN add operation to unlock the file.
Also fixed the .resx file being added to the project prematurely and not being added to SVN when multiple designer views for the same form are opened before the .resx file has been saved to disk for the first time.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/05/2009">Fix SD2-1584 - VB .NET snippet parser crashes on invalid syntax</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/05/2009">Fix SD2-1587 - Duplicate sections added to solution file on each save</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="09/05/2009">fixed SD2-1526 - Save As shows a Save As dialog box for each view attached to the file</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="09/05/2009">Disabled project resources in the python form designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="09/04/2009">Added missing resource strings for the profiler</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="09/04/2009">- Top 20 displays user code only
- Added functionality to expand selected hot paths
- fixed percentage of parent</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/04/2009">Temporarily disable FileChangeWatcher while renaming files. Should fix forum-10029.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="09/03/2009">missed to commit some changes (never commit around 12 PM!)</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="09/03/2009">Profiler:
- added translation for the profiler UI
- added functionality to control data collection (only profile parts)
- added new columns (Time spent (self); Time spent/call, Time spent (self)/call)
- added hot path indicators
- Top 20 tab is now sorted by TimeSpentSelf

* fixed bug in LocalizeExtension</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="09/03/2009">Profiler:
- added new data columns
- added hot path indicator if method takes more than 20% time of the parent node</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="09/02/2009">RC 2 designation of setup</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/02/2009">Reparse when return is pressed.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="09/02/2009">Profiler: fixed "Find references" for methods without source code</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="09/02/2009">implemented Find References for the profiler tree view</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="09/02/2009">Profiler:
- fixed memory leak
- removed ICSharpCode.SharpDevelop.Profiling namespace
- added filter for unit tests when selecting "Run with profiler"</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/01/2009">Set /32BIT+ on booc.exe</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/01/2009">Missing StringParser.Parse call in ApplicationSettings panel</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/01/2009">Put new build options into the UI (BOO-1228)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="09/01/2009">Update to Boo 0.9.2.3383.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/31/2009">Code coverage results now read from new PartCover 2.3's new results file format.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/30/2009">Update COM Guids written to registry for PartCover 2.3</Change>
  <Change author="Christian Hornung" date="08/29/2009">Forms designer: Fixed SD2-1531 - CenterHorizontally / CenterVertically: icons are swapped.</Change>
  <Change author="Christian Hornung" date="08/29/2009">NRefactoryASTConvertVisitor: Apply IndexerNameAttributes to the names of the converted indexers.
This fixes the ReflectorAddIn being unable to find such indexers in Reflector.</Change>
  <Change author="Christian Hornung" date="08/29/2009">ReflectorAddIn: Fixed finding nested classes and members thereof.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/28/2009">profiler: modified DefaultProfiler implementation to show error message instead of throwing NotSupportedException in case no profiler was found.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/28/2009">Create new projects as x86 by default - AnyCPU leads to programs running as 64-bit process without ever being tested that way.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/28/2009">Fix unit tests.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/28/2009">Replace equals sign with space to match new PartCover command line syntax.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/28/2009">Upgrade to PartCover 2.3.
Set /32BIT flag on PartCover.exe</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/27/2009">Change label "Goto line number" -&gt; "Go to" to better reflect the features of the new GotoDialog</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="08/24/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/PrettyPrintOptions.cs:
* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/CSharpOutputVisitor.cs: Added brace
  forcement options - this enables to change bracing for some
  constructs. </Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/23/2009">Python code converter now attempts to detect property references and adds a this reference.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/23/2009">Python code converter now converts type reference expressions.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/23/2009">Python code converter now supports read-only and write-only property conversions.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/22/2009">Python forms designer now supports negative doubles as method parameters.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/20/2009">Fixed SD2-1494 - 'Move class to file' duplicates delegate declarations
Based on patch by Bruno Marques.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/20/2009">Fixed bug in python forms designer failing to convert an integer into a double when loading a form with a property of type double.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/20/2009">Python forms designer now generating AnchorStyles properties.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/19/2009">Fixed output for overloaded unary operators.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/19/2009">Fixed SD2-1572 - operators are shown as nameless methods in code completion</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/19/2009">Don't generate code for attributes of base class in override code completion.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/19/2009">Python forms designer shows a more useful error message if it is unable to find a type to create a local variable.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/19/2009">Fixed SD2-1581 - GetterModifiers/SetterModifiers not loaded in ReflectionProperty and CecilReader</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/18/2009">Python forms designer now calls all methods and explicit interface methods when loading InitializeComponent method.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/17/2009">Fixed squashed controls on debug symbols options panel.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/16/2009">Python forms designer now converts constructor parameters to the correct objects when loading a form.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/16/2009">Python form designer now supports assigning a local variable to a property on a control.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/16/2009">Fixed null reference exception in form designer's NameCreationService when generating code with the python code dom serializer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/15/2009">Python forms designer now generates code using a code dom serializer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/15/2009">Fixed NullReferenceException in unit tests pad when SharpDevelop was closed while the parser thread was still running.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/14/2009">Fixed SD2-1582: Code completion lists multiple entries for partial classes</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/11/2009">Rename ProjectTypeGuids.cs to work around bug in Visual Studio. (http://community.sharpdevelop.net/forums/t/9580.aspx)</Change>
  <Change author="Christian Hornung" date="08/11/2009">TextArea: Always set the owner of the tooltip when shown.
Fixes SD2-1543 - Text editor tooltips only work in the file opened first when secondary monitor present.
Also fixes problems with showing tooltips when TextEditors are used on different levels in the form hierarchy within the same application.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/10/2009">Python forms designer now generates code for the content of nested custom collections.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/10/2009">Python forms designer now generates code for the items inside a custom collection on a control.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/09/2009">Added support for TableLayoutPanel RowStyles and ColumnStyles in Python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/08/2009">Child controls on a TableLayoutPanel are now supported in the Python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/08/2009">Fixed null reference exception in the python forms designer when generating code for properties that have a null property value.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/08/2009">Python forms designer now generates a multline string for the RichTextBox.Text property.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/08/2009">Filename with dot character is now correctly shown in the Errors window when compiling a python file that has syntax errors.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/07/2009">Recompiled SharpSvn using VS2008.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="08/07/2009">Update to SharpSvn 1.6004.1329. (SVN 1.6.4)</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/06/2009">Python forms designer can now load a SplitContainer containing child controls.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/05/2009">MonthCalendar SelectionRange and DateTime[] properties now supported in Python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/04/2009">Added support for list view groups in Python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/03/2009">Python forms designer now uses InstanceDescriptor to generate code for object creation.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/02/2009">Fixed null reference exception when generating code in the Python forms designer for a non-IComponent object's AddRange method.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/01/2009">Inherited tooltips now supported in the Python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/01/2009">Public inherited controls now supported in Python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="08/01/2009">Inherited protected controls are now supported in the Python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/31/2009">Fixed SD2-1465 - Convert integer casts correctly between VB and C#</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/31/2009">Fixed forum-9858: problem with sizeof operator converting from C# to VB.NET</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/29/2009">Fixed null reference exception when loading/generating code in the python forms designer when a control's property was null.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/29/2009">Python forms designer no longer generates code for controls in inherited base class.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/28/2009">Python forms designer now creates an instance of the form's base class instead of just a Form or UserControl when loading a form in the designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/28/2009">Fixed forum-9843: missing icon in project browser for .resx files.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/27/2009">Python forms designer can now design forms that do not directly inherit from Form or UserControl.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="07/27/2009">Profiler: fixed display of meta data tokens VAR and MVAR</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/26/2009">Refactored the set property value code out of the PythonComponentWalker class.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/26/2009">Fixed failing unit test in Python addin.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/26/2009">Python forms designer now loading/generating forms with nested properties (e.g. Button.FlatAppearance)</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/26/2009">Correct code generated for Default cursor in python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/25/2009">Installer now displays SharpDevelop 3.1 RC 1.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/25/2009">Handle SVN errors when creating a new project.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/25/2009">Two tree nodes with their NodeFont property set can now be loaded into the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/25/2009">Fixed build.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/25/2009">Fixed SD2-1406: More Missing String Resources</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/25/2009">Fixed SD2-1525: Error creating new files when default encoding was set to Unicode.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/24/2009">Fixed SD2-1550 - Exception creating new F# project when F# compiler is not installed</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/24/2009">Fixed InvalidOperationException in ReflectorAddIn when the 'run as administrator' compatibility option is set on Reflector.exe.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/24/2009">Disable upgrades from SharpDevelop 3.0 to 3.1 (the user will be prompted to uninstall 3.0 first). Fixes SD2-1565 - Microsoft.Scripting.dll removed by upgrade 3.0 -&gt; 3.1.
Upgrading from previous 3.1 beta versions are still possible.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/24/2009">Fixed parsing of try statements with multiple catch clauses (bug introduced in r4526).</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/24/2009">* Src/Visitors/LookupTableVisitor.cs: Lookup table visitors now can
  be re-used (they reset when they visit a compilation unit).</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/24/2009">* Src/Parser/CSharp/cs.ATG:
* Src/Parser/CSharp/Parser.cs: Catch clauses have now set their
  correct positions.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/23/2009">Fixed bug where some TreeNode properties were not set when loading a form into the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/23/2009">* Src/Visitors/LookupTableVisitor.cs: Catch variable declarations
  are now valid in the whole catch clause, not only in the statement
  block. (Required for the lookup inside the variable declaration)</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/22/2009">Updated to IronPython 2.0.2</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/19/2009">Show version number of installed 3rd party AddIns in exception dialog.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/19/2009">Added support for code folding of global python methods defined outside of a class.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/18/2009">Use svn:eol-style=native for NRefactory.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/18/2009">CSharpOutputTest: don't ignore whitespace.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/17/2009">Consistently use "http://schemas.microsoft.com/winfx/2006/xaml/presentation" as WPF XML namespace.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/17/2009">Made text boxes for Postbuild/Prebuild events multi-line (forum-9791).</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/17/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/OutputFormatter.cs:
* Src/PrettyPrinter/AbstractOutputFormatter.cs: Comments that start
  line are no longer indented when outputting them.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/17/2009">Setup: Fixed issue in .booproj file association.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/17/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/CSharpOutputVisitor.cs: Corrected else in
  new line placement.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="07/17/2009">fixed SD2-1551</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/17/2009">Changed GUID for Microsoft.Scripting.dll</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/17/2009">Fixed forum-9335: checked state in FileTypeRegisterer option panel is incorrect for some entries.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/17/2009">TaskView: show paths relative to the solution directory</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/17/2009">Mark SdaUser sample as 32-bit.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/17/2009">Make "Open in explorer" available for solution items and directories.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/17/2009">Fixed forum-9732: exception opening F# interactive pad.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/17/2009">Fixed bug introduced in revision 4452 (IOException on startup).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/17/2009">Fixed SD2-893 - Searching text in a directory with no access permissions throws exception</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/16/2009">Fixed potential ArgumentNullException in search (forum-9109, though I couldn't reproduce it).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/16/2009">NRefactory: Fixed incorrect end column in C# type declarations.
Fixes forum-9578: IndexOutOfRangeException in 'Implement Interface' refactoring.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/16/2009">Fixed copying from ICSharpCode.TextEditor to wordpad (encode of characters that are not in Windows-1252).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/16/2009">Fixed forum-9591: NUnit test results are read with incorrect encoding.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/16/2009">Fixed forum-9717: exception using Project - Add - New Folder when the project browser is not open.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/15/2009">Fixed bug when converting references to 'this' and event handlers to python.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/15/2009">Fixed null reference exception when converting a constructor to python.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/13/2009">* Src/Visitors/AbstractAstTransformer.cs: Made node stack protected.
  I had a complicated AST transformation where I needed to add/remove
  statements this seemed to be the easiest solution for it.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/12/2009">Fixed thread-safety problem in DefaultReturnType.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/09/2009">Updated to NUnit 2.5.1</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/09/2009">Fixed build.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="07/07/2009">Fixed thread-safety problem in SearchClassReturnType.
Don't set 'Strict' to true when creating new Boo project.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="07/07/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/CSharpOutputVisitor.cs: Improved
  collection initializer output.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/06/2009">ListViewItems with imageIndex or imageKey set are now created correctly in generated python forms designer code.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/05/2009">Updated to the final build of WiX 3.0 (3.0.5419)</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/05/2009">Child tree nodes now added on loading a form in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/04/2009">Code now generated for TreeView TreeNodes in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="07/01/2009">Code generation and ImageList resources now supported in python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/30/2009">FileUtility.IsValidPath(...) and additional directory tests (patch by Frederick Kautz)</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/29/2009">Added support for icon resources in python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/29/2009">Added some missing IronPython files.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/29/2009">Bitmap resources on the main form are now supported in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/27/2009">Python forms designer now generating the correct code when assigning a DataSet to a DataGridView's DataSource.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/27/2009">Python forms designer now supports local bitmap resources.</Change>
  <Change author="Robert Pickering" date="06/25/2009">Fix breaking changes from may CTP.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="06/23/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/PrettyPrintOptions.cs:
* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/CSharpOutputVisitor.cs: Added anonymous
  method brace style.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/22/2009">Fixed NRefactory unit tests.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="06/22/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/CSharpOutputVisitor.cs: Removed
  unneccessary spaces in if section.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/21/2009">Empty form resource file (.resx) now being created and added to project when the python forms designer is used.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/21/2009">Fixed failing unit test.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="06/19/2009">* Output/CSharp/VBNetToCSharpConverterTest.cs: Fixed unit test.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="06/18/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/OutputFormatter.cs:
* Src/PrettyPrinter/AbstractOutputFormatter.cs: Corrected block
  comment output.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="06/18/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/CSharpOutputVisitor.cs: If statements
  without block are now correctly indented.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/17/2009">Python code converter now supports xml doc comments for constructors. Xml doc comments that are not before a class, method or constructor declaration are converted to single line python comments.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="06/17/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/CSharpOutputVisitor.cs: removed embedded
  statement newline. (newline here is incorrect ex. printing "if (a)
  Foo(); else Bar();" should be possible without forcing newline after
  Foo).</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="06/17/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/CSharpOutputVisitor.cs: Correctly indent
  embedded statements.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/16/2009">Convert class and method xml doc comments to python docstrings.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/14/2009">Added support for multiline comments in the python code converter.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/14/2009">Single line comments now converted from C#, VB.NET to Python.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/09/2009">Python forms designer now ignores any statements before the form's InitializeComponent method is found (e.g. sys.path.append('...').</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/08/2009">Avoid NullReferenceException when pasting text.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/07/2009">Add 'import clr' if clr.GetType used in converted python code.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/07/2009">Xor operator now converted to python correctly.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/07/2009">Python converter no longer uses 'self' when calling a method inside a static method.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/07/2009">Python code converter now adds code to call the project's main entry method.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/07/2009">Python code converter now converts 'foreach (string key in dictionary.Keys)' statements correctly.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/07/2009">Now using short type names (e.g. Array instead of System.Array) in generated python code.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/06/2009">Convert System.String and System.Int32 to 'str' and 'int' in python.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/06/2009">New line added between import statements and class definitions when converting code to Python.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/06/2009">Fixed code completion on protected members from a base class when the inheritance was specified in a different part of a partial class.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/06/2009">Fixed ObjectDisposedException if user closes SharpDevelop while LoadSolutionProjects thread is running.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/05/2009">Updated fullAssemblyNameToRequiredFrameworkVersionDictionary.
Increase timeout on ProcessExitedTestFixture.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="06/05/2009">- added additional logging to Unit Test profiling
- fixed bug in Extract Method</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="06/04/2009">Profiler: reimplemented search in QueryView</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/04/2009">Double quote characters now escaped when generating string property assignments in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/04/2009">Backslash characters now escaped when generating string property assignments in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/04/2009">Correct code generated for nested enum types (e.g. Environment.SpecialFolder) in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/04/2009">Simplified Reflector AddIn by using Reflector's SendMessage API instead of registering the IPC AddIn.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/04/2009">Fixed another performance issue in the ClassBrowser.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/03/2009">Fixed performance issue in class browser during loading of a solution.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/03/2009">Performance improvements for solution loading:
- Fixed bug in SVN OverlayIconManager that could cause two worker threads to be started.
- Fixed performance bug in SvnClientWrapper.SingleStatus.
- DefaultProjectContent.AddClassToNamespaceListInternal: do not try to update existing class in namespace's classList if we're adding a new class.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/03/2009">Profiler: Fixed CPU usage graph in time line.
Profiler: Fixed "go to definition" command.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="06/03/2009">Break statements no longer generated when converting a switch statement to python.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/03/2009">Fixed exception in VB code completion when a C# project contains two namespaces that differ only in case.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/03/2009">Allow setting 'Option Infer' in project options.
Create new projects with 'Option Infer' set to true.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/02/2009">Allow choosing the target framework when creating VB projects.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/02/2009">Add Project Reference dialog: sort projects alphabetically.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="06/01/2009">Fixed ArgumentNullException in CompileModifiedProjectsOnly when an IBuildable2 implementation returned null as ProjectBuildOptions.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/31/2009">Do not show 'Finalize' in C# code completion.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/31/2009">Use tabs instead of spaces in WPF file templates.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/31/2009">Python code converter now specifies types when creating an instance of a generic.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/31/2009">Python forms designer no longer generates code for the form's MainMenuStrip property after the menu strip has been removed.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/30/2009">Python menu options now use the debugger when running ipy.exe</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/27/2009">Debugger now supports debugging IronPython code.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/27/2009">Namespace imports now import all classes on conversion to IronPython.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/26/2009">MainFile property now set when converting a project to IronPython.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/25/2009">Boolean variables now correctly converted to python.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/25/2009">Added support for ContextMenuStrips in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/24/2009">Extender provider properties set for other controls now appear in properties window in the python form designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/24/2009">Rename "Quality Tools" -&gt; "Analysis".</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/23/2009">Added Create XML output file option to the options panel for unit tests.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/23/2009">Added support for extender providers (e.g. ToolTips) in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/21/2009">Update to Mono.Cecil revision 134535.
Fixed handling of type attribute arguments when loading with Mono.Cecil.
Fixed handling of unbound generic types in type attribute arguments when loading with Reflection.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/21/2009">Python forms designer does not generate comments for a control if no property or event handler code was generated for that control.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="05/20/2009">fixed VB .NET Indentation: multiline statements indented correctly (forums/t/9532)</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="05/19/2009">- fixed bugs with profiling read-only projects and Unit Tests
- fixed bug in UnitTesting-AddIn, if unit testing was canceled before the execution had started</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/18/2009">Disabled failing debugger test.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/18/2009">Added support for ISupportInitialize in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="05/18/2009">- added basic support for profiling Unit Tests
- fixed bug in CopyStacktrace</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/17/2009">Python forms designer now checks the non-visual component has a constructor that takes an IContainer before generating code to create the component.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/16/2009">Do not save the highlighter being used if the user didn't change it.
Fixed SD2-1540: When "build only modified projects" is used, projects are not rebuilt after a "Clean" operation</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/14/2009">Updated language resources.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/14/2009">Unit Tests tree now shows tests that fail due to an unhandled exception being thrown.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/14/2009">Installer now displays SharpDevelop 3.1 Beta 1.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="05/13/2009">removed transparency from DebuggeeExceptionForm, added buttons for Break and Terminate again</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/13/2009">Fixed ArgumentException thrown when duplicate binary file ids are in a WiX file and the dialog is opened in the designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/12/2009">NUnit-Console no longer creates TestResult.xml if the /xml option is not used.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/12/2009">SvnClientWrapper: Fixed NullReferenceException in discovery of changed paths.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/10/2009">Static class methods now use staticmethod when converted to Python.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/10/2009">Use HintPath for IronPython reference in Python project templates.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/10/2009">Add reference to IronPython when converting projects to Python.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/09/2009">Typeof expressions and for each loops using a method call now converted to Python.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/09/2009">Event handlers with EventHandler object creation now converted to Python.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/09/2009">An error message is now displayed when trying to compile a Python application when no main file is specified.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/09/2009">Can now convert C# and VB.NET projects to Python.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/09/2009">Fixed SD2-1514 - Exception compiling F# project using build worker.
Custom events are no longer forwarded to the SharpDevelop process.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="05/08/2009">WatchPad now allows changing nodes while debugging</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/08/2009">Updated to WiX 3.0.5301</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="05/08/2009">Added ICSharpCode.Core.Presentation to assembly redirect list.
DebuggeeExceptionForm: ShowInTaskbar = false</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="05/08/2009">fixed bug in CSharpMethodExtractor</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/07/2009">Fixed build - NUnit 2.5 no longer allows hiding the SetUpFixture method in derived classes.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/06/2009">Fixed failing tests due to move to NUnit 2.5</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/06/2009">Updated to NUnit 2.5.0.9122</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="05/06/2009">fixed bug when using other file sizes than 64 mb for temporary storage file.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/04/2009">Added basic support for non-visual components in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/04/2009">Python forms designer now supports loading and generating code for the text in a ListViewSubItem.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/04/2009">Ordering of controls in generated python forms designer code now matches the order of the standard forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="05/03/2009">Python forms designer now supports generating code for ListViewItem's text.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="05/03/2009">Created new ExceptionForm based on suggestions from forums/9446</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="05/02/2009">Extract Method: clean up and bug fixes</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="05/02/2009">Extract Method: Add ref keyword to extracted parameters only if the type is a reference type</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="05/02/2009">- fixed bugs in VB .NET Indentation
- added Unit Tests</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="05/01/2009">prepared profiler for public testing</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/27/2009">Show 'static' class modifier in tool tips.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/27/2009">Use a Mutex when accessing SharpDevelopProperties.xml

Prevents IOException when shutting down multiple SharpDevelop instances at the same time.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/27/2009">Subversion History View: immediately get file name from view content</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="04/26/2009">- declared PrimaryFileName in AbstractViewContent as virtual to make special case in Profiler ViewContent working</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/25/2009">Fixed forum-9315: view contents with customized save command (e.g. project options) are not saved when closing them and clicking 'Yes' in the 'Do you want to save?' question.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/25/2009">Fixed potential NullReferenceException in MemberLookupHelper.IsInvocable. Might have been the cause of forum-9346.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/25/2009">Use "build modified projects only" feature when starting unit tests.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/25/2009">CopyToClipboard: don't truncate string to 256 characters</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/25/2009">F# binding: use "--standalone" option only in release builds. This speeds up compiling debug builds of SharpDevelop.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/25/2009">Force handle creation of main form in WorkbenchSingleton.InitializeWorkbench.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="04/25/2009">Python forms designer no longer generates event handlers if they already exist.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/25/2009">Fixed namespace handling in Boo ConvertVisitor.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/25/2009">Prevent Boo forms designer from changing the type of fields to 'void'</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/25/2009">Boo Forms Designer: prevent the designer from deleting unrelated fields.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/25/2009">Fixed loading of assemblies that contain generic types with more than 10 type parameters.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/25/2009">Adjust ProjectTypeGuids when converting project between C# and VB.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/24/2009">Fixed SD2-1397 - Code completion does not work for nested classes inside generic classes.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/24/2009">Fixed bug in ScriptRunner (for scripts inside file or project templates).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/24/2009">Fixed bug in build engine: the mapping solution configuration-&gt;project configuration was not applied when building only modified projects.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="04/24/2009">* Src/Lexer/AbstractLexer.cs: Allow white spaces as symbol
  separator.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="04/20/2009">- fixed crash in ExtractedMethod, when extracting code with params parameters
- always close undo group, even if extraction causes exception</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="04/19/2009">- Bug fixes in Profiler and enhancements in GUI
- improved TaskListPad</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/19/2009">ICSharpCode.SharpDevelop.BuildWorker: Fixed excessive CPU usage during build worker shutdown.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="04/19/2009">Added limited support for ListView items in the python forms designer. No support for sub items nor the ListViewItem.Text property.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="04/18/2009">Code coverage results now generated when an exclusion has been added to the project.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/17/2009">Fixed forum-9381: GetClass could return class with incorrect type parameter count.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="04/15/2009">fixed bugs in ProfileProject and ProfileExecutableForm</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="04/13/2009">Added support for designing user controls in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="04/13/2009">Removed all control specific code when determining child components in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="04/13/2009">Updated UI
Added context menu to RingDiagramControl</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="04/13/2009">Removed control specific code from generated code when adding an array of controls to a property in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="04/12/2009">Form.Controls, MenuStrip.Items and ToolStripMenuItem.DropDownItems properties are now generated in the correct alphabetical order in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="04/12/2009">Controls.Add method is now invoked rather than being hard coded in the python forms designer code.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="04/12/2009">ComboBox items code now generated in Python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="04/12/2009">fixed display of merged nodes in profiler</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="04/12/2009">Fixed build by using actual ToolStripMenuItem sizes in menustrip test.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="04/12/2009">Python forms designer now handles loading and generating a form with a MenuStrip and ToolStripItems.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="04/11/2009">Fixed bug in XmlParser.IsAttributeValueChar not recognising valid characters as being valid for an attribute value.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/11/2009">Allow saving external tool options when tools in the .NET SDK cannot be found.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/10/2009">SubversionAddIn: on 64-bit Windows, look for 64-bit version of TortoiseSVN.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/10/2009">Improved performance of UpdateAssemblyInfo.
Code-completion debug output: use Debug.WriteLine instead of Console.WriteLine.
Custom Tool project template: fixed compile error.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="04/10/2009">- fixed SD2-1523 - Watch pad right click shows two context menus based on patch from http://community.sharpdevelop.net/forums/t/9006.aspx
- applied patch for drag&amp;drop in Watch pad from http://community.sharpdevelop.net/forums/t/9320.aspx
- fixed NullReferenceException in ValueNode if either Watch Pad or LocalVarPad are not opened (added comments)
</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="04/09/2009">Fixed SD2-1505 - Locals window - show values in hex does not refresh the values on display. Based on fix supplied by Nikhil Sarda.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="04/08/2009">Added empty string checks to XmlParser.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="04/07/2009">fixed crash when trying to profile non-.NET executable
fixed crash when trying to open a session without datasets
fixed bug in HexEditor</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="04/03/2009">added work-around for Windows Forms bug in ElementHost, because WpfViewer was sometimes not displayed.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="04/03/2009">Switch from SvnDotNet to SharpSVN. This updates the embedded subversion library from 1.5.0 to 1.6.0.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="04/03/2009">fixed CallCount when selecting only a small amount of datasets.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="04/02/2009">Code code now generated for empty menu strip in python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/31/2009">Python form designer now supports loading/generating code for a form's AcceptButton and CancelButton properties.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="03/31/2009">* Parser/Expressions/LambdaExpressionTests.cs: Added test case for
  typed ref/out parameter lambda expressions.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="03/31/2009">* Src/Parser/gen.sh:
* Src/Parser/CSharp/cs.ATG:
* Src/Parser/CSharp/Parser.cs:
* Src/Parser/CSharp/CSharpParser.cs: Added ref/out parameters for
  typed lambda expressions.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="03/30/2009">fixed threading bug in QueryCompiler</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/30/2009">Event handlers added for child controls when loading a form into the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/30/2009">XmlParser now returning the correct active element if the element is followed by a tab or new line character.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="03/30/2009">* Src/Lexer/CSharp/Lexer.cs:
* Src/Lexer/AbstractLexer.cs: #if/#elif preprocessor directive now
  contain the arg as string representation too (arg was null).</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/29/2009">Form event handlers now generated and loaded by python form designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/28/2009">SuspendLayout, ResumeLayout methods now called for nested controls in python forms designer generated code.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/28/2009">Child controls now added to a panel when form is loaded into the python form designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/28/2009">Code is now generated for controls added to a panel in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="03/27/2009">* Src/Visitors/LookupTableVisitor.cs: Added IsQueryContinuation flag
  to local lookup variables. This helps resolving the type of "from
  ... where ... into VAR" constructs.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/27/2009">When unpinning a pad, hide it immediately (patch from DockPanelSuite forum).</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="03/26/2009">fixed bugs in UI
updated TODO.txt</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/26/2009">Added support for AnchorStyles in python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="03/25/2009">Improvements and bug fixes in Profiler.AddIn GUI</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/25/2009">Python forms designer: Control creation code now generated. Control variable names now prefixed with underscore. Control properties now set correctly on loading the form into the designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="03/24/2009">Moved SharpDevelopElementHost to Profiler.AddIn
Added new functionality to Profiler
rearranged ProfileExecutableForm
fixed bug in TimeLineControl
smaller bug fixes</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/24/2009">ChangeLog: only show changes since revision 3800.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="03/24/2009">Added SharpDevelopElementHost for hosting WPF controls as ViewContents</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/24/2009">Code now generated for controls on a form in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/22/2009">The state of ShowErrors, ShowWarnings, ShowMessages in the Errors window is now saved on closing SharpDevelop.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/22/2009">Python forms designer now using more PropertyDescriptor information to determine whether a property should be serialized. Form properties now generated in alphabetical order.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/22/2009">Added python class library project template.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="03/21/2009">new options in profiler</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/21/2009">Fixed failing python addin unit tests - font size now converted to string using CultureInfo.InvariantCulture.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/21/2009">Python forms designer now supports fonts.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/20/2009">Prevent potential stack overflow in ElementReturnType.BaseType.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/20/2009">Fixed SD2-1534: Boo forms designer modifies fields in non-designer file</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/20/2009">Fixed bug introduced in last commit (fixes unit tests).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/20/2009">Fixed SD2-1530: protected inner classes are not visible</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/20/2009">Don't constantly create new threads to poll the clipboard.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/20/2009">Fixed SD2-1533 - Project configurations get confused</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/20/2009">Work around for SD2-1485: Build worker occasionally hangs:
In parallel builds, don't use in-process build.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="03/19/2009">- bug fixes
- added "ProfileExecutable" dialog
- replaced ProfilerService with ProfilerRunner</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/19/2009">Fixed unhandled FileNotFoundException in XML tree editor when a file is loaded with a dtd reference that cannot be found.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/19/2009">Fixed bug in 'Find overrides': when overrides were in partial classes, the search result sometimes used the wrong class part.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/19/2009">Fixed exception from forum-9214 (but hung build still not fixed).
Fixed string resource name in App.Config description.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/18/2009">Can now run all tests with code coverage or run all the tests in the current project.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="03/18/2009">- finished Options Panels
- bug fixes</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/18/2009">Mark booc.exe as 32-bit (fix build).
DynamicHelpPad: fixed possible NullReferenceException.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/18/2009">Fixed forum-9168: ArgumentOutOfRangeException in BooFormattingStrategy.SearchBracketForward/GapTextBufferStrategy.GetCharAt.
Fixed forum-9200: ArgumentException in ShowErrorHelpCommand.Run/IHxTopicList.ItemAt.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/18/2009">Boo: In strict mode, the default visibility is private.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/18/2009">Update to Boo 0.9.1.3287.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/18/2009">SearchAndReplace: don't search in .exe/.dll/.pdb</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/17/2009">Python forms designer now supports Form Color properties.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="03/17/2009">added "QualityTools" menu</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="03/17/2009">fixed profiler start bugs</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/17/2009">Revert changes to NRefactory.csproj in revision 3849 - add GlobalAssemblyInfo.cs back so that the assembly is correctly versioned.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="03/17/2009">* Src/Lexer/AbstractLexer.cs: Added null check.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="03/17/2009">* Src/Lexer/ILexer.cs:
* Src/Lexer/CSharp/Lexer.cs:
* Src/Lexer/AbstractLexer.cs: Added SetConditionalCompilationSymbols
  method.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/16/2009">Added CreateStartInfo method to AbstractProject.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/16/2009">When handling file names, use StringComparison.OrdinalIgnoreCase instead of InvariantCultureIgnoreCase.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/16/2009">ExceptionBox: fixed potential deadlock when exception occurred on non-GUI thread.
Added menu entries for "Edit &gt; Insert &gt; Paste as comment/string" (r3832)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/16/2009">Fixed cleanup in AutomatedBuild.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/16/2009">Add profiler to setup.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/16/2009">Build profiler when using SharpDevelop .bat files.</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="03/16/2009">removed doc
fixed references in Profiler.AddIn
clean up in allocator.cpp</Change>
  <Change author="Siegfried Pammer" date="03/16/2009">Added Profiler</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="03/16/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/OutputFormatter.cs:
* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/PrettyPrintOptions.cs:
* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/CSharpOutputVisitor.cs: Added place on new
  line options.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="03/16/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/CSharpOutputVisitor.cs: fixed bracket
  space output issues.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="03/15/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/OutputFormatter.cs:
* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/PrettyPrintOptions.cs:
* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/CSharpOutputVisitor.cs: Added some
  formatting options.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/14/2009">Python forms designer now supports Control's Padding property.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/14/2009">Python forms designer now supports the Form's Location property.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/14/2009">Python forms designer now supports AutoScrollMinSize, AutoScrollMargin and MinimumSize properties.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="03/13/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/CSharpOutputVisitor.cs: Respected the
  aroundassignment option in more constructs.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="03/13/2009">* NRefactory.csproj: 

* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/OutputFormatter.cs:
* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/PrettyPrintOptions.cs:
* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/CSharpOutputVisitor.cs: Added some options.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="03/13/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/PrettyPrintOptions.cs:
* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/CSharpOutputVisitor.cs: Added some output
  options.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/13/2009">Form.Visible property now loaded/generated in python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/12/2009">Python forms designer now supports loading and generating code for standard control cursors (e.g. AppStarting, Help and WaitCursor).</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="03/10/2009">* Src/Parser/IParser.cs:
* Src/Lexer/VBNet/Lexer.cs:
* Src/Lexer/CSharp/Lexer.cs:
* Src/Lexer/AbstractLexer.cs:
* Src/Parser/AbstractParser.cs:
* Src/Lexer/Special/Comment.cs:
* Src/Parser/VBNet/VBNetParser.cs:
* Src/Lexer/Special/TagComment.cs:
* Src/Parser/CSharp/CSharpParser.cs:
* Src/Lexer/Special/SpecialTracker.cs:
* Src/Lexer/CSharp/ConditionalCompilation.cs:
* Src/Lexer/Special/PreProcessingDirective.cs:
* Src/PrettyPrinter/AbstractOutputFormatter.cs:
* Src/PrettyPrinter/CSharp/CSharpOutputVisitor.cs: Added some
  nrefactory features for monodevelop.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="03/09/2009">* Output/SnippetConversion.cs:
* Output/VBNet/CSharpToVBNetConverterTest.cs:
* Output/CSharp/VBNetToCSharpConverterTest.cs: Fixed some unit tests
  so that they run on non windows platforms.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="03/09/2009">* Src/PrettyPrinter/VBNet/VBNetOutputFormatter.cs: Use
  Environment.Newline instead of hardcoded eol terminator.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/08/2009">String, enum and boolean properties on a form now loading and being generated in the python forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/08/2009">mscorlib now added as a default reference in Python project templates.</Change>
  <Change author="Christian Hornung" date="03/07/2009">Fixed SD2-1529 - Forms designer rewrites array field declarations.
Fixed NRefactory -&gt; CodeDOM output for array types.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/06/2009">New feature: Edit &gt; Insert &gt; Paste as comment/string.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/01/2009">Fixed namespace handling in Boo code completion.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="03/01/2009">Assembly created when compiling a class library is now copied to the output folder.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="03/01/2009">When using "Compile modified projects only", require recompilation if the project options were changed.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/28/2009">Handle errors when writing new class diagram (fixes forum-9024: Read only class diagram file causing System.UnauthorizedAccessException)</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/28/2009">Fixed exception when an open solution file is deleted.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/28/2009">Fixed SD2-1524: Reference to a method hiding a base class event resolved incorrectly.
Add Subversion "Get lock..." command.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/28/2009">Fixed SD2-1528: Stack overflow in code completion when using FluentValidation</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/27/2009">Add DispatcherErrorHandler allow WPF addins to use SharpDevelop's unhandled exception dialog.
Fixed expected output in failing NRefactory unit test.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="02/27/2009">* cs.ATG:
* Parser.cs: Fixed unit tests.</Change>
  <Change author="Mike Krüger" date="02/26/2009">checked in some changes from monodevelop.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/23/2009">Added some strings to the translation database (mostly message box texts in the Subversion AddIn).</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/23/2009">Backport ICSharpCode.Core.Presentation to SharpDevelop 3.1 - this makes it easier to write WPF-based AddIns.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/22/2009">Open With dialog is now centered and no longer shown in task bar.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/21/2009">Fixed bug in "Find references": MemberLookupHelper.IsSimilarMember could return true when comparing a field with a local variable.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/21/2009">Fixed subversion state condition for directory/solution nodes.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/18/2009">Pressing the up key in the Python Console no longer closes the completion window if there is command history.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/17/2009">Make DisplayBindingService public.
Change keyboard shortcut for debug-mode code completion to Ctrl+Space+Alt+Dot (debug builds only).</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/16/2009">Updated the installer version number to 3.1</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/15/2009">Enabled the python code conversion and forms designer.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/15/2009">Updated to IronPython 2.0.1</Change>
  <Change author="David Srbecký" date="02/14/2009">Updated test output for ".NET Framework 3.5 SP1 Family Update"</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/14/2009">Fixed null reference exception in WriteableProjectEvaluator if a null IProject is returned from the ProjectService.CurrentProject.</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/14/2009">Catch InvalidCastException in IronPython parser when parsing invalid code.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/12/2009">SD2-1521: Reconsider what a 'preinstalled addin' is.
Third-party AddIns installed in SharpDevelop/AddIns are now visible in the AddInManager, only AddIns with 'addInManagerHidden="preinstalled"' stay hidden.</Change>
  <Change author="Daniel Grunwald" date="02/10/2009">Allow SharpDevelop 3.0 addins to load in SharpDevelop 3.1.
Continue using 'SharpDevelop3.0' directory for settings in SharpDevelop 3.1.</Change>
  <Change author="Christoph Wille" date="02/10/2009">Version 3.1 designation</Change>
  <Change author="Matt Ward" date="02/09/2009">Updated string resources.</Change>
</ChangeLog>